<page>
<url>/authors/index.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : corrupt press authors Diana S. Adams, author of Catch, is an Edmonton, Alberta based writer with work published in a variety of journals and several anthologies. She studied English & Philosophy at the University of Guelph before picking up a Culinary Arts degree in Toronto. After working ten years in Finance as a money market trader, Diana now works from home with three kids, three dogs and a cat. Science Fiction creeps up into her work as a tour of sorts/through alternate reality. Suzanne Allen, author of Verisimilitude, is the Creative Writing and Literature Program Director for WICE and a co–editor of issue.ZERO, an upstart literary magazine created as an offshoot of the Anglo writing scene in Paris. Her poems can be found in The Translator’s French Quarter, Nerve Cowboy, Pearl, California Quarterly, Cider Press Review, Spot Literary Magazine, Upstairs at Duroc, and in the anthologies Not a Muse: the inner lives of women, a world poetry anthology, (Haven Books, 2009) and Strangers in Paris: New Writing Inspired by the City of Light (Tightrope Books, 2011). She was recently nominated for a Pushcart Prize. Filippa Bahrke, author of ELSEWHERE, is a graduate from Greenwich University, where she studied English Lit and Creative Writing. Her poems have previously featured in the student magazine. She was the winner of the 2016 PNSEL Poetry Prize. She is originally from Sweden, and has settled in Paris. J. Bradley, author of How Esmeralda Estrus Got Her Revenge, is the Interviews Editor of PANK Magazine and lives at iheartfailure.net. Sarah Chapman, author by Sky + +, is twenty–five years old and lives in London. Her poems have appeared online and in print. It’s something I seem to be concerned with when writing poetry, that thing where you are so close to someone but not actually there. Emily Critchley, author by IMAGINARYLOVEPOEMS, was born in Athens, Greece in 1980 and grew up in Dorset. She holds a PhD in contemporary, American, women’s poetry and philosophy from the University of Cambridge and is the author of several poetry books. Critchley teaches English and Creative Writing at the University of Greenwich, London. Anamaría Crowe Serrano, author of KALEIDOgraph (with Nina Karacosta) and one columbus leap, is Irish and lives in Dublin where she works as a language teacher and translator of contemporary poetry from Spanish and Italian. In 2008, Shearsman published her first full–length collection, Femispheres. She is a frequent reader of her work in Ireland and abroad, and is the recipient of two awards from the Arts Council of Ireland. steven dalachinsky, author of Long Play E.P. the complete Evan Parker Poems, was born in 1946, Brooklyn, New York. His work has appeared extensively in journals and anthologies. He has written liner notes for many artists. His CDs, chapbooks and books have garnered praise and prizes. He has read throughout the N.Y. area, the U.S., Japan and Europe, including France and Germany. He is active in the mail–art circuit & has shown his collages in Poets’ Collages shows. Jennifer K Dick is the author of Lilith, Circuits, Betwixt, Fluorescence (Univ. of Georgia Press, 2004), the ebook Enclosures (BlazeVox, 2007) & the chapbooks Tracery (Dusie Kollectiv 5, 2012), Retina/Rètine (Estepa Editions, Paris, 2005) & Conversion (Estepa Editions, Paris, Sept 2013 with artwork by Kate Van Houten). She has work in the trilingual collective Ondulations (Aeneis, 2009) & 6 anthologies, most recently 12 x 12: Conversations in 21st Century Poetry & Poetics (Univ. of Iowa Press, 2009). Her translations of French poets have been published in various magazines and included in the New European Poets (Graywolf, 2008) anthology. Currently a poetry editor for VERSAL Magazine out of Amsterdam, Jennifer also co–urates the bilingual IVY Writers Paris reading series, co–organizes the Ecrire l’Art French poetry residency at La Kunsthalle Mulhouse, writes a regular poetics column for the UK magazine ‘Tears in The Fence’ called ‘Of Tradition and Experiment’ & reviews for ‘Drunken Boat’. An academic teaching at the Université de Haute Alsace, Mulhouse, Jennifer is the co–editor with Stephanie Schwerter of ‘Transmissibility and Cultural Transfer: Dimensions of Translation in the Humanities’ (Ibidem Verlag, Stuttgart, 2012) & the French volume ‘Traduire — transmettre ou trahir — Rèflexions sur la traduction en sciences humaines’ (Fall 2013, éditions de la Maison des sciences de l’homme, Paris). She and Ocèane Delleaux are also querying publishers for their newly completed edition of theoretical and visual texts from their 2012 conference ‘Lex–ICON: treating the image as text & the text as image’. For more information & links to poems and critical work online, please see Jennifer’s blog at jenniferkdick.blogspot.com. Alexander Dickow, author of Trial Balloons, writes and translates in French and English, and is the author of Caramboles (Paris: Argol Editions, 2008). He is an assistant professor of French at Virginia Tech. He also enjoys hiking and tropical fruit. William J. Doan, author of orantes linguis, is an Associate Dean and Professor of Theatre at Penn State University. He holds a BA from Gannon University, an MFA from Virginia Commonwealth University and a Ph.D. from Case Western Reserve University. Megan Fernandes, author of Organ Speech, researches English Literature at the University of California, Santa Barbara, where she founded and runs the Poetry/Poetics Hub. Her family comes from Tanzania. Bonny Finberg is the author of Dèja Vu. Her work has been translated into French, Japanese and Hungarian. Publisher’s Weekly said that her fiction in Best American Erotica ‘exudes a stunning sensual sensibility.’ Her fiction, poetry and reviews have been published in numerous print and online journals and anthologies including the Outlaw Bible of American Poetry (Thundersmouth), Evergreen Review, four Unbearables anthologies (Autonomedia) and Lost and Found: New York Stories from Mr. Beller’s Neighborhood. She is a contributor to A Gathering of Tribes, Sensitive Skin, The Brooklyn Rail, Le Purple Journal, Upstairs at Duroc, and Van Gogh’s Ear. Her collection,’How the Discovery of Sugar Produced the Romantic Era,’ is featured in the video 5 Guys Read Finberg. Her photography has been published both in print and online art journals and exhibits, including ‘A Book About Death’ (Emily Harvey Gallery, NY) ‘Seeking Kali,’ Davka and A Gathering of Tribes. Her written work and visual art are archived in the ‘Downtown Writers’ collection at the NYU Fales library. She lives in Paris and New York, and is working on her second novel. kit fryatt, author of turn push | turn pull, was born in Iran, & grew up in England, Turkey and Singapore. She moved to Ireland in 1999, stayed there for nearly 13 years and now lives in Scotland. She runs wurm im apfel and wurm press. Arpine Konyalian Grenier, author of The Silent G, was born and raised in Beirut, Lebanon after the post–Ottoman era induced French rule of the region ended. She spent the summers with her family in the Kessab province of Syria where her maternal grandparents (Apelians) had been landowner for centuries. Her father, Krikor was an orphan from Konya. She holds graduate degrees from the American University of Beirut, and the Milton Avery Graduate School of the Arts, Bard College. Academic and corporate years were devoted to cardiovascular research, human resources development, and regulatory finance. She wrote during lunch breaks and the weekend, music first then poetry. Her work has appeared in numerous publications, often awarded or as finalist. Other credits include multi–disciplinary collaborations, guest editing, and co–convening or presenting at conferences. Amy Hollowell, the author of Giacomettrics and Peneloping, is an American–born Parisian poet, journalist and translator. She helped edit the Paris–based review Pharos, founded by Alice Notley and the late Douglas Oliver, and is a former student of the Jack Kerouac School of Disembodied Poetics at Naropa University in Boulder, Colorado. In 2004, she founded the Wild Flower Zen group, which she continues to lead in France and Portugal. Having worked as a diamond messenger, busker, storyteller, tutor and theatre performer, Bibi Jacob, the author of Glittery City, is now settled in the City of Light as a voice actor. She regularly performs her work and also campaigns for the environment through her site www.plastikdiet.com. James Jewell, the author of Ships Made of Fake Fur, is a singer songwriter, poet and writer, originally from Pennsylvania, who has spent much of the last two years living in Paris. There, he was inspired by writers and poets, from Spoken Word Paris, Shakespeare and Co., and Poets Live, to build a body of poetry and short fiction. Nina Karacosta, author of KALEIDOgraph (with Anamaría Crowe Serrano) and Previous Vertigos (translated into French as Vertiges Prècèdents by Anne Talvaz), is an actor and poet. Born in Athens, she moved to London in 1993, to New York City in 1995 and later to Paris in 2009, which she now considers home. She has degrees in Physics from the University of Patras Greece and in Theater from Webber Douglas Academy of Dramatics Arts in London. Since 2003 she has studied with many exuberant living poets (Ann Waldman, Alice Notley , Marge Piercy, Simon Pettet, Sparrow) at the Poetry Project and the Poets House in New York. She has performed her work at the Poetry Project at St. Mark’s Church, the Cornelia St. Cafè, Bowery Poetry Club, with the Ollin Imagination theatre collective. She has also been involved in performance using text, voice and sound. She performed for a couple of years with the avant–garde chorus Vox Risk Holler addressing anti–war issues lead by performance artist Lynn Book. Work of hers has appeared in Pomegranate Seeds: An Anthology of Greek–American Poetry, Best of Stain Anthology, Surreal–zine, The Melancholy Dane, The Smoking book, Ditch and Upstairs at Duroc. John Kliphan, author of LOW LEVEL FLYING, died in 2012. He spent most of his life in Paris, where he founded and ran Live Poets, which gave much encouragement to young poets, helping them develop their craft. Christophe Lamiot Enos, author of The Sun Brings, was born in Beaumont–le–Roger in France, spent over fifteen years in English–speaking countries and now lives in Paris. He’s had two literary essays and seven verse narratives published in France and elsewhere, including four by Flammarion, Paris, in the ‘Poèsie’ collection directed by Yves di Manno. Anthony Liccione, author of Wolf Down, was born in Chicago, Illinois and raised in Rochester, New York. He grew up in a broken family, moving from family member to family member. In his teens, he lived with friends, strangers, in a vacant house, a vacant garage, and finally inside his car (when he got his 12th grade diploma). He achieved an Associates in Architecture, but withdrew from a Bachelors in English to become a father. In his early twenties he met rapper/writer Brian Parker, who introduced him to, and encouraged him to write, poetry. After many years in New York, he now lives in Ft. Worth, Texas with his two children. He works for the power company and serves for the Army National Guard part–time. Pansy Maurer–Alvarez, author of IN A FORM OF SUSPENSION and ANT–SMALL AND AMOROUS, was born in Puerto Rico, grew up in Pennsylvania and has lived in Europe since 1973. She did her literary studies at universities in the US, Spain and Switzerland. Her poetry has appeared in several anthologies and numerous magazines in Austria, France, Spain, Switzerland, the UK and the US and some of her poems have been translated into French, German and Spanish. Her collections are DOLORES: THE ALPINE YEARS and WHEN THE BODY SAYS IT’S LEAVING (both from Hanging Loose Press, Brooklyn); and LOVERS ETERNALLY NEARING, a collaboration with the Swiss artist Walter Ehrismann, with German translations by Rudolf Bähler (Editions Thomas Howeg, Zürich). She is a Contributing Editor for the British magazine Tears in the Fence. She lives in Paris, mainly, and Zürich, sometimes. rob mclennan, author of author of Miss Canada, was born in and lives in Ottawa, Canada’s ‘glorious capital city’. He is the author of more than twenty trade books of poetry, fiction and non–fiction. An editor and publisher, he runs above/ground press, Chaudiere Books (with Jennifer Mulligan), The Garneau Review, seventeen seconds: a journal of poetry and poetics and the Ottawa poetry pdf annual ottawater. He spent the 2007–8 academic year in Edmonton as writer–in–residence at the University of Alberta, and regularly posts reviews, essays, interviews and other notices at robmclennan.blogspot.com. Meghan McNealy, author of limite dèsir, is a Pataphysician, poet, performer, playwright, printer, papermaker, and polyglot. She is a New England–born Acadian who earned her Bachelor’s Degree in Liberal Arts from The Evergreen State College. Her texts have appeared in Wheelhouse, BirdDog, Admit2, and Slightly West; she has illustrated Nothings Houses:Prefab Eulogies by David Wolach [BlazeVox, 2010] and Collobert Orbital by Johan Johnson [Displaced Press, 2009]; her original performances have been staged at the literary conference, Press: Activism & The Avant–Garde as well as the 2010 Olympia Film Festival, Thèatre de Verre in Paris, and The Art Factory in Buenos Aires. Rod Mengham, author of The Understory, is Reader in Modern English Literature at the University of Cambridge, where he is also Curator of Works of Art at Jesus College. He is the author of books on Charles Dickens, Emily Bronte and Henry Green, as well as of The Descent of Language (1993). He has edited collections of essays on contemporary fiction, violence and avant-garde art, and the fiction of the 1940s. He is also the editor of the Equipage series of poetry pamphlets. Kate Noakes, Welsh Academician, author of I–spy and shanty, lives mainly in Paris, where she is co–founder of Paris Lit Up, a non–profit literary association. She blogs at boomslangpoetry.blogspot.com. This is her fourth collection of poetry. A native of Michigan, Michelle Noteboom is the author of Roadkill, The Chia Letters (Dusie Kollektiv 2009), Edging (Cracked Slab Books), which won the 2006 Heartland Poetry Prize, and Hors–cage, in French translation by Frédéric Forte (Éditions de l’Attente, 2010). She’s lived in Paris since 1991 where she co–founded and helped curated the bilingual reading series Ivy Writers Paris for many years. lars palm, author of road song for, lives with his lovely wife, currently in Malmö, he has lived in any number of other places, like Dublin & Las Palmas de Gran Canaria, as well. In all those places he insists & has insisted on cooking, wandering aimlessly & writing poems. He has published 22 books in English, and 10 in Swedish. Jay Passer, b. 1965, author of At The End Of The Street, is a native San Franciscan, schooled in the gutter muse and service–industry bard, seen most often haunting the public house, city library and long pavement of the metropolis. Themes of anarchy, delirium, antiestablishment ethos and bawdy street survival all cast lots in the spectrum of his vision. Passer’s work first appeared in Caliban magazine, alongside notable beats and future luminaries, in 1988. Pearl Pirie, author of Mammals of Hoarfrost, is Canadian. Her writing was recently published in ditch, anthology 4 (canadian) (innovative poets), PRECIPICe, Dandelion, This Magazine, unarmed, 1cent and Lantern: A Teacher’s Guide to Writing Haiku and Related Literary Forms. Thirsts, now a book, won the 2011 Robert Kroetsch Award for innovative Poetry. For more information, browse pearlpirie.com. Rufo Quintavalle, author of hhereenow, Shelf, 1–15, moral hazard and the chemical sweats and Dog, cock, ape and viper, was born in London in 1978 and lives in Paris. He is the author of the chapbooks Make Nothing Happen (Oystercatcher Press, 2009) and Liquiddity (Oystercatcher Press, 2011). He is poetry editor for the webzine nthposition. Freke Räihä, author and translator of Standard Form for Language Resentment, is mainly preoccupied with structures and patterns; curating and transgressing literature and also the embedding and dissolving of its hierarchies. R L Raymond, author of Weakdays, is a writer from London, Ontario. His poems and stories have appeared in dozens of literary and underground journals. When not writing, he runs PigeonBike Press. He holds an MA in English Literature from the University of Western Ontario. Monty Reid, author of Garden (dec unit), is a well–known Canadian poet. He lives in Ottawa, where he was, until recently, the Director of Exhibitions at the Canadian Museum of Nature. He now writes and gardens full time. Lily Robert–Foley, author of m, was born in 1975 in New Brunswick, Canada. She was transcriber and annotator for The North Georgia Gazette (2009, Green Lantern Press), and engineer of graphemachine (Xexoxial Editions 2013, Xerolage chapbook). She teaches Anglophone literature and translation at the Universiteé d’Angers in France. The current work consists of rewritten notes from her dissertation research (at Paris 8) on the self–translation of Beckett. Greg Santos, author of TWEET TWEET TWEET, is a poet and writing instructor originally from Montreal. He holds an MFA in Creative Writing from The New School in Manhattan. He is the poetry editor of the journal pax americana and on the editorial board of the Paris–based journal Upstairs at Duroc. Greg’s debut poetry collection, The Emperor’s Sofa, was longlisted for the ReLit Awards. He lives in New Haven with his wife and daughter. He runs moondoggy’s pad. justina semetaite, author of Parted, was born in Lithuania in 1989, and lives in London. She has recently completed her BA in Creative Writing and now studies International Publishing at City University. M. K. Sukach, author of Impression of a Life, resides in Washington DC with his wife, Chris, and dog, Scribble. MK retired as an Air Force officer and veteran of the wars in Iraq and Afghanistan. His website is http://www.mksukach.com/. Alex Stolis, author of Left of the Dial, lives in Minneapolis. He has had poems published in numerous journals. He has been the recipient of five Pushcart Nominations. Anne Talvaz, translator of ANT–SMALL AND AMOROUS and Vertiges Prècèdents into French, was born in Brussels in 1963 and lives near Paris. She has lived in China and Brazil, and is the author of 3 poetry collections, a novel, and a travel book. Born in Ohio, George Vance, author of A SHORT CIRCUIT and XMAS COLLAGE, has lived in Paris for the last 30 years. He has also resided in Vienna, Aachen, Brussels and the French overseas possession New Caledonia (Kanaky). He has read at numerous Paris venues and his work has been published in Upstairs at Duroc, Pharos, the on–line magazines Ekleksopgraphia, Nth position and Retort. A regular contributor to the poetry blog REWORDS, he is also the creator of the video installation ‘Heights of Experience’. Vance continues to work on text/image fusion and street art experiments. Patrick Williamson, author of Gifted and Bacon, Bits & Buriton, is an English poet who was born in Madrid in 1960 and lives near Paris. His early years were spent abroad, but the family home in the UK was in Buriton, Hampshire. He spent time in Soho in the late ‘80s. In 1995 and 2003 he was an invited poet at the Festival International de Poèsie at Trois–Riviéres, in Quèbec. reuben woolley, author of some time we are heroes, was born in Chesterfield, UK, and lived and worked in Zaragoza, Spain, where he died in 2019. He has been published in various print and online magazines such as Tears in the Fence, The Lighthouse Literary Journal, The Interpreter’s House’, Domestic Cherry, The Stare’s Nest, Ink Sweat and Tears, The Poetry Shed, Nutshells and Nuggets, Yellow Chair Review, Bone Orchard Poetry, and The Goose. He edited two online magazines, I am not a silent poet for protest poems about abuse, and The Curly Mind for exploratory work. Nicolette Wong, author of Stone Bride Madrigals, is a dancer, magician and editor–in–chief of A–Minor Magazine and Press. Her work has appeared in E–ratio, Thrush Poetry, Escape Into Life, fwriction review, and other journals. She lives in Hong Kong. Lebanese–American poet and writer Rewa Zeinati, author of Bullets & Orchids, was raised in Lebanon, UAE and USA. She studied English Literature at the American University of Beirut, Lebanon, and earned her MFA in Creative Writing from the University of Missouri, Saint Louis, USA. Several of her poems, essays, interviews and translations have been published in literary journals & anthologies in the US, UK, Middle East and online. She is the founding editor and publisher of Sukoon Magazine (www.sukoonmag.com), the first Arab–themed, English language online literary journal in the Arab region. Rewa works in advertising and lives with a nice man whom the world agrees is her husband, in Dubai, where she constantly worries over the frail health of her growing garden herb, Basil. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>authors</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>corrupt press poetry publisher luxembourg esch-sur-alzette english</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/ant.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Pansy Maurer–Alvarez ANT—SMALL AND AMOROUS In English and French, traduit de l’anglais (Etats–Unis) par Anne Talvaz US Trade, 64pp, €12, January 2012 ISBN 979–10–90394–06–3 The cover image is “59” collage, 2010 by Sarah Petlin. I deeply admire the intelligent and passionate poetry of Pansy Maurer–Alvarez. … Perhaps paradoxically, as a poet she is both distant and painfully close, chilly and burning, … In a quiet way, her poems even have the ability to make ordinary words strange. Elinor Nauen Pansy Maurer–Alvarez is … able to translate all the seen and unseen promptings of the day into colorful, sometimes surreal, imagery and musical lines. Harvey Shapiro : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>ANT—SMALL AND AMOROUS</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/betwixt.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Jennifer K. Dick Betwixt A5, 30pp, €5, May 2011 ISBN 979–10–90394–03–2 The cover image is “Mirror Mirror”, a two plate solar etching by Michele Winkler. ‘Betwixt’ penetrates deeply beneath and betwixt the narrative of Orpheus and Eurydice. These intermediate and indeterminate spin-offs from the motif are set in a stuttering, probing movement that is ever present in an ongoing gaze that is both backward and forward-looking. The transformative registers and play that Dick draws upon incites the reader through linguistic and sonic verve to question the framework and creases of male and female identity and to see the fragility of pastoral stability and the proximity of loss. Her voice is unerring and unmasking. I love it. David Caddy, editor of Tears in the Fence “In the ec-, ec- ectoplasm of the echo,” Jennifer K. Dick’s new concerto sings vibrato, rocking us boldly into shadowscape of the serpentine underworld of starboard saints the order of Orpheus and Eurydice, those Hansels and Gretels. Lushly and lavishly into the underworld we descend to look and to never look back, to forage forward and toward her lyrical horizon, sinking cock-eared and then tipping into her dreamscapes, begging, “make it double,” please. Sandy Florian, author of The Tree of No In the sinuous descents of Jennifer K. Dick’s Betwixt, we are among the debris of doxa not left to lie around an ailing modernist Thames or Rhime, but rather bound up again in the fascicle of a deeper myth-going gauntlet. Eurydice is the by-proxy birth of the lyric, of both its sad and smiling aspects (the marriage ceremony and the broken quest), two divided faces which both promise never to look back. Sex and scalpel, fusion and fissuring, no identity is left unknit in this astonishing revival. So we too may go deeper, into the passages of our choosing: “just follow the tracks in the dark, steady, steadying.” Nicholas Manning, author of Novaless In Jennifer K. Dick’s wonderful rewinding of “loosely wound” myth, Orpheus and Eurydice are strung out on contemporary anxieties and pulled through the compelling lines of a tensely rhythmic language, an element at once familiar and strange. Description is unsteady, under revision, and flatness and depth make sudden shifts the characters (including reader and writer) negotiate, making forward movement exciting: the stakes are still high, even as we’re reminded the game is lost. Meanwhile the field of the author’s attention is mobile, errant, including the frame or what takes place elsewhere, beyond (around, askew to) a “story.” The subject of this splendid collection is the texture of understanding in its uneasy motion through the “sonorous dark”—in other words, the work of love. Laura Mullen Jennifer K. Dick’s Betwixt occurs at intermission—the point at which one act is made historical even as another supplants it. Inside this book, Eurydice and Orpheus wander the streets of Paris (which is also New York), Hades looks strangely like the Metro, and everything pickpockets the attributes of everything else. “Already what’s awaiting is rerouted,” Dick writes, as the tectonics of identity shift, destabilize and reconstitute, ushering forth a postmodern noir that sizzles with cosmopolitan smarts. Just further proof that poetry, like life, brooks no stasis: all is syncopation. Chris Pusateri, author of Anon Betwixt is a contemporary myth. It’s a “gaze cast,” where the unseen are momentarily seen—within shadow, under the pale light. It’s a dicey game of chance, in which time folds in on itself. Intimacy is held captive and released: “To: think only of her. Not to forget: she is. To: know this.” The impulse to turn leaves us standing still. In awe. Marveling at Jennifer K. Dick’s “condensation of meaning.” Michelle Naka Pierce, author of Beloved Integer These poems reward several readings, evoking each time a different aspect of the multi-layered complexities of our worlds, both old and new. Read Afric McGlinchey’s full review at Sabotage Reviews. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Betwixt</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/bulletsorchids.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Rewa Zeinati Bullets & Orchids A5, 24pp, €5, June 2013 ISBN 979-10-90394-41-4 The cover image is by dylan harris. Stunning text exquisitely tuned to the traumas/torments/delicate presences of our (utterly mysterious but knowable, in smaller ways) times. In 58 spare, but enormous segments of poetry, Rewa Zeinati transports and elevates her readers into and beyond the confounding. It is rare to read text that feels like such a full breath. Naomi Shihab Nye This is not your usual quiet, well mannered, little poetry book. In fact, it may not be a poetry book. It is most probably a journey: one where you can follow the workings of an intelligent mind on its surreal path through past and present, family and current day Middle East. This is not a book that will spoon-feed you. There is a refusal to give you words that you don’t need. There are no explanations. You are expected to be grown up. But OMG, the images. “I saw bullets though. Many were shaped like tongues.” You need to be on board this trip. Me? I’m going round again. This woman is the real deal. Frank Dullaghan As the Arab street meets the determination of country to remain unchanged or even to re-invent the past, Rewa Zeinati keeps asking “where will it go from here?” In this amazing poetry sequence, nothing familiar remains, unless it be the fact that all aspects of our lives intersect: marriage, divorce, devotion to tradition, passion for change. The voice pushing out the declarations in this poetry turns to a syntax of interruption, one that remakes the Arab world in the speaker’s own image: fresh, honest, questioning, and challenging. Above all, this fervent poetry represents the latest flowering of the Middle East, surprising yet unstoppable, betokening individual life. Steven M. Schreiner A raw and gripping new voice. Nathalie Handal : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Bullets & Orchids</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/buriton.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Patrick Williamson Bacon, Bits, & Buriton A5, 28pp, January 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-22-3 Striking, slightly off-key or quirky images rub shoulders with an intensity of feeling and experience…. intricacy of style, strong authorial presence and descriptive and narrative edginess. Alan Hardy, NHI Review : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Bacon, Bits, & Buriton</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/catch.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Diana S. Adams Catch A5, 24pp, €5, June 2013 ISBN 979-10-90394-40-7 The cover image is by dylan harris. I don’t know too many poets who could find beauty in reticence. It’s eerie in the way Diana S. Adams manages to turn the dramatic pause into something as special as a personal revelation. She’s the mistress of the herky–jerky procession. Her line breaks stun us with their warped generosity, their cautious love. Steve Fellner, pansypoetics.blogspot.com Here are the many–fold surprises found in conflicting worlds, rendered with such subtlety of phrasing and a wholly alarming availability. These poetic gifts make for a kind of heightened awareness, even as we fall rather helplessly into each of these miniatures. One is reminded of the way Ritsos has of unsettling us with narrative, reaching deep into the emotions, and even deeper into the unconscious. Diana S. Adams dreams up poems that are so richly alive with the small dramas that turn large in our sleep, where time and space wait, suspended. Jeffrey Levine, author of Jubilo : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Catch</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/chemical.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : rufo quintavalle moral hazard and the chemical sweats A5, 40pp, €8, December 2013 ISBN 979-10-90394-44-5 The cover image is by the author. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>moral hazard and the chemical sweats</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/circuits.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Jennifer K. Dick Circuits US Trade, 80pp, €12, March 2013 ISBN 979-10-90394-30-8 The cover image is reproduced courtesy of Fred R. Dee, M.D. Dick is renowned for her speed of thought and recitation. Here there is speed and also a slower experiential and spatial deliberation that marks a new maturity in her work. The reader senses the body, a life with disruption and fluidity, and wit permeating a flamboyant yet precise mapping and probing. Tears in the Fence In Circuits, Jennifer K. Dick engagingly writes—as in thinking around—how the idea of neural biology, brain research, technological advancement, and literature impact on the epistemological us of us. Is this our world, or our re-created world we are looking into while it is starring back at us head on? This is mutual co-creation—relation—reflection, where the author restlessly lands one precise word at a time only to move off quickly like a neural firing—which jolts, as poetry does best, the reader’s wires into new thinking! To have this book included in one’s library is a “no-brainer”—so to speak. Joe Ross Memory as the revel of physical bonds. Memory as a space broken into by time. Memory as the morning dew of places. Memory as the electrical map of traces. In Jennifer K. Dick’s Circuits, memory inks the pathways of reading into—as in rereading ourselves, as in remembering our bodies, as in rewriting the earthbound motherboard. A procedural tour de force—both an inhabitation and absorption of neurologist George Johnson’s seminal In the Palaces of Memory—Dick’s Circuits seeks the physical pulse that links information to duration. Turkish spices, clatter of China, there’s a story to be told about the mapping of the brain, meaning Lynch, Cooper, Johnson, meaning love, Paris, Northampton, meaning enzymes in mutiny, chemicals with Kinase C. Language comes to rescue the mouth from obscurity: “A particle and its physics explains why candles were the roads and parks emptied, blurring up the slick-with-guilt.” Turns out nothing is obscure and everything’s connected; theory is alive in the substance of the wiring, and Jennifer K. Dick is writing the code. Matthew Cooperman : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Circuits</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/dcav.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Rufo Quintavalle Dog, cock, ape and viper pocket book, 104pp, €12, June 2011 ISBN 979-10-90394-02-5 There is no other contemporary English poet quite like Quintavalle: from his extraordinary name (perhaps the most inherently exciting since “Ezra Pound”) to his exotically-imagined, deeply-thoughtful, ruefully witty, and sometimes very brief, poems, to his slightly marginalised location across the Channel, he represents a different current—one that, should he continue to write as well over the next few years, will establish him, one hopes, as a key British poet of the 2010s. Todd Swift Lapidary and wry, Rufo Quintavalle’s poetry is distinctive. It often combines a playful stance with a steely stare in ways which may disconcert the newcomer. Yet its unmistakable style is a result of a scrupulous ethics of attention and saying – an approach which successfully sidesteps all unquestioned assumptions about the written and the thought. Peter Hughes, Oystercatcher Press : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Dog, cock, ape and viper</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/dejavu.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Bonny Finberg Déja Vu A5, 36pp, colour, September 2011, €8 ISBN 979-10-90394-15-5 The cover image is “Déja Vu” by the author. In Déja Vu Bonny Finberg cracks open the disparateness that makes up the unlikely assemblage known as “I” as well as its many adjacent and tangential beings. The poet’s memory is both hers and others, including the Meat Soldier. The poems are visceral and kaleidoscopic, sensual and disturbing. Not only is Novel in 24 Chapters magnificent, but it serves as a key to the rest of the book. Each poem is another chapter in a novel without a beginning, middle, or end, a novel which embraces language in all its soulful ecstasy and wintry cheerlessness, the highs and lows of being alive and open in these perilous times. As Ted Berrigan used to say—It’s Terrific. John Yau I’m reminded of Plath, Shapcott and Selima Hill. There are similarities to experimental poets; Emily Critchley comes to mind. But there’s also a considerable freshness to Finberg’s work, particularly when her use of photographic art is taken into account. She is, I’m sure, a poet we’ll be reading much more from in the future. I strongly recommend buying this pamphlet. Lindsay Holland, Sabotage Reviews. Bonny Finberg’s evocative narrative-imagery seeps through the eyes, settling comfortably in the mind. It rises like a heat mirage with an internal dream logic worthy of Anais Nin. Déja Vu is marked by beauty, concision and, most importantly, a profound wisdom, tempered by keen humor and satiric wit, that can only be attained through encounters with the divine. Darius James The déja vu in this collection is the act of magic one rarely finds in the interplay of image and word. In this powerful book Finberg provides her dual magic by presenting photos that, though surreal, make us feel rooted in place. Poems that, while rooted in the “real,” display dreamlike qualities. Both ground us, yet pull us away from the mundane, to the unlimited possibilities of the here and now. Steve Dalachinsky : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Déja Vu</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/elsewhere.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Filippa Bahrke ELSEWHERE A5, 20pp, December 2016, €6 ISBN 979-10-90394-55-1 The cover image is by Agnes Binett. Bahrke’s lyric explorations here both cleverly and beautifully interrogate the status of the self vis a vis the ‘other’ in a transnational world: I chase I of no accents and washed out flags Can we lie down here till the snow turns to straw start a new language I want to unlearn Wipe those clouded yesterdays from off my eyes The borderlessness of her themes mirrors this writer’s refusal to choose between either daring experimentalism or lyric beauty, when both are ‘ours to ride’. Hooray for this wonderful maiden voyage, this ‘route / of belief in elsewhere’! Emily Critchley The young Swedish writer, Filippa Bahrke, wouldn’t be the first person to have fallen in love, moved to Paris and published a book of poems. But as far as I know she is the only one to have stolen the fat apple from the mouth of capitalism’s swollen pig and woken up to discover that “the turkey we stuffed/ has stuffed us”. This is a promising debut and a reminder that if you are looking for what might constitute European literature in these troubled post–Brexit days then corrupt press and its sprawling catalogue of trans–national, contemporary poetry is as good a place as any to turn. Rufo Quintavalle, member of Oulipo : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>ELSEWHERE</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/endofstreet.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Jay Passer At The End Of The Street A5, 32pp, €5, June 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-28-5 The cover image is by dylan harris. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>At The End Of The Street</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/esmeralda.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : J. Bradley How Esmerelda Estrus Got Her Revenge A5, 28pp, September 2011, €5 ISBN 979-10-90394-09-4 What do the words ‘epic poem’ conjure up for you? Thoughts of gods, myths and battles – Beowulf, Homer, Dante and Milton perhaps? Maybe you think of Pound, Carlos Williams and Walcott, each of whom adapted and modernised the epic form. Most people probably don’t think of sex, vernacular language and frequent references to popular culture, all of which J. Bradley’s How Esmerelda Estrus Got Her Revenge has in abundance. … Overall, it’s a seething, dark romp of a poem. Accessible and fun, truthful and surprising, Bradley’s pamphlet hooked me from the start. I’m particularly reminded of Jane Holland’s Boudicca & Co. There are also similarities to some of Neil Rollinson’s work, perhaps with a side order of Eliot. This is a captivating poem for the 21st century. Anyone with an interest in contemporary, intelligent narrative poetry should buy this book. Lindsay Holland, Sabotage Reviews. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>How Esmerelda Estrus Got Her Revenge</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/garden.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Monty Reid Garden (dec unit) A5, 28pp, €5, May 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-21-6 The cover image is from diciembre by Andrea Bula. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Garden (dec unit)</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/gia.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Amy Hollowell Giacomettrics US Trade, 80pp, €12, November 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-34-4 The cover image is by the author. Amy Hollowell’s spindly and spiky (but never frail) ekphrastic experiments succeed in carrying the uncanny, galvanic power of Giacometti’s sculpture into verbal forms. Kit Fryatt : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Giacomettrics</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/gifted.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Patrick Williamson Gifted A5, 36pp, €8, September 2014 ISBN 979-10-90394-53-7 From starry heavens to the gates of hell, from teeth to cups: these poems will pursue the reader along a journey through a terrifying and fascinating landscape, both physical and psychological. The voice of these poems, both disembodied and all too present, acts as our guide through the world these poems inhabit, making sure we see exactly what he wishes to point out in the world of Gifted. It is a testament to the power of this language and this poetry that this world feels both utterly real and entirely conjured. Andrea Janelle Dickens : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Gifted</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/glittery.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Bibi Jacob Glittery City A5, 20pp, €5 First edition: September 2013 Second edition: May 2014 ISBN 979-10-90394-42-1 The cover image is by Sarah Vivienne York. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Glittery City</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/hen.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : rufo quintavalle hhereenow US Trade, 88pp, €15, autumn 2016 ISBN 979-10-90394-57-5 The cover image is by the author. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>hhereenow</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/hole.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Troy Yorke Hole In My Side: Redemption of the Moon-Hooker US Trade, 132pp, €15, November 2014 ISBN 979-10-90394-29-2 The cover image is by Troy Yorke. Troy Yorke’s poetry is a sensual and confrontational experience that tickles not only the ear, but also the eye through it’s imaginative layout on the page. The language is rich with imagery that is both visceral and delightfully earthy and vulgar. It speaks of the contemporary experience of sex, love, violence and desire with a clear, twinkling eye that makes each selection something to be savoured again and again. This is a book I would highly recommend. Brad Fraser, Writer/Director i love ths book th amayzing love pomes ar palpable sum surprising th big pickshur pomes ar also remarkabul “awestruck” ovrwhelming th vizual pomes ar sew wundrful lifts th reedr byond a wundrful work daring incisiv n rapturous bill bissett, ‘poet n paintr’ Troy Yorke says it best in his poem “Wandering Eye Thru a Waterfall”; these poems are “one rip-roaring rush of wrong splashed hard up the forbidden…” They leak and they harp like beautifully plucked high-strung ball-breaking ballads. They howl like randy wolverines rabid with wit and foresight. Bearing concise debauched glimpses of life, splashed with lurid and luscious observations that would make a moon-hooker blush with inter-galactic bliss—if you just lie down and suck back these poems “behind a pale sheet of nobody” they will leave you choking—and gasping—for more. David Bateman, Performance Poet : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Hole In My Side: Redemption of the Moon-Hooker</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/imaginary.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Emily Critchley IMAGINARYLOVEPOEMS A5, 36pp, €5, December 2011 ISBN 979-10-90394-17-9 These are poems that love their poetic history and sweep you off your page. They contain wings reigning over sleepy echoes, temporary motion, ornamental self, all but true. Imaginary love in poem gardens toads. Whatever happens after all stays here and jiggles about for your reading pleasure. Ian Patterson The queen of the Greenwich world time writes, with the cut of a grace that can be heard all over the hill, to the end to impossibly sexy growth. Nobody, especially “here among men”, will get round or past it. Quietness is a vector of real courage they don”t yet think, a male Opheliac obliterates the nunnery. The only realistic thing right now, not scared to suppose supposed green, is this. This weakness stronger than any ithyphallos, a pop-up militia in the dungeon sky, and no simple war left in it. This book. This book by Emily makes me think about the beautiful things we can still do. Care, and what ‘future growth’ would really be. Parisian pariciding. Richness of spirit for ‘half perfectly again’. Not just hard questions. It’s what ‘happens when my standing reserve: you?’ flies too close: ‘There is still time’. It’s that courage is not what you think. Jonty Tiplady : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>IMAGINARYLOVEPOEMS</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/impression.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : M. K. Sukach Impression of a Life A5, 28pp, €6, September 2014 ISBN 979-10-90394-51-3 The cover image is by dylan harris. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Impression of a Life</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/ispyshanty.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Kate Noakes I-spy and shanty US Trade, 96pp, €15, March 2014 ISBN 979-10-90394-45-2 The cover image is by dylan harris. Kate Noakes’ poetry has always treasured vivid language, and does so here—just savour her nectar–sipping bat that ‘gigolos away the dark’. But this rich and varied new collection also strikes a new note, as quietly compact as the water–worn stones that appear in several poems, spare but alive with implications, like a whole life in wartime conveyed by ‘And now / the kissing away of two long winters. Him here.’ Philip Gross Kate Noakes is a poet on the road, on the wing, in transit, yet rooted in place,childhood, family, love. She records detail as in a journal, gathering experience, words,traveller’s tales. A pebble is ‘a travelling spot’ that ends as ‘nothing but light’, teller of Earth’s journey. The pebble’s beginning is the poet’s beginning, a child pond–dipping, picking up stones. A memorable poem records her grandfather throwing his medals into the river on his way home from the war, as if horror could be washed away. It survives in his grand–daughter’s imagination, and in her vivid poems. Gillian Clarke : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>I-spy and shanty</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/kg.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Nina Karacosta & Anamaría Crowe Serrano KALEIDOgraph US Trade, 38pp, €15, spring 2017 ISBN 979-10-90394-56-8 This book is book is beautiful—καλός beautiful; εἶδος form. Thee poems are both within and without themselves; style succumbs to stylus and the two voices become so many that authorship seems to collapse. But there is order, startlingly so, connections that are delightful to trace—arising accidentally but expertly managed by the obvious inherent and learned skills of the poets. You will be safe here if it’s meaning you want, excited if you want to play: “the hidden gets lost / and the lost gets gotten”. Windows, eyes and mirrors are important, space, dreams, masks; they bring you anew to old ground–to cows, school, Harcourt street station, a recycling vagrant. Think of the titles as lenses and the words as clever, shifting patterns. Open the senses. Let the poem surround you. These beautiful semantic graphics are wise, witty and, to quote Sylvia Plath, ‘irrefutable’. Máighréad Medbh As the words of this KALEIDOgraph shift and slant, spinning their incandescent spell, three languages stealthily become one—marvelously elusive yet splendidly sonorous and deeply true. Amy Hollowell Based on a chance encounter, mutual liking and an unusual trilingual project between both poets, this collection is an unqualified success. Witty yet kindly, intelligent and thoroughly addictive. Anne Ortiz Talvaz Shrewd and effervescent, KALEIDOgraph is a collaboration consistently alert to verbal possibilities and power, creating (in the words of the poem ‘sneachta’) ‘a language constantly correlating tongues’. Kit Fryatt Crossing linguistic boundaries…Gaelic & Greek…and English more than liberally tossed in to make an appetizing yet filling international amalgam…Nina Karacosta and Anamaría Crowe Serrano criss cross linguistic boundaries with aplomb, fluidly, fluently and great agility like the (wo)men on the flying trapeze? While keeping all associations loose they ironically turn out spot on poetry, allusions defined, imagination intuitively tuned in…pleasures and surprises galore got me riffng involved in their play, fun, beauty brilliantly satisfying…had me cheering them on in their collaborative ventures… lydia cortes These eloquent “guesses” intertwine like clematis! Sparrow : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>KALEIDOgraph</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/left.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Alex Stolis Left of the Dial A5, 28pp, €6, January 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-50-6 The cover image is Left of the Dial by Georgia Rifa. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Left of the Dial</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/lilith.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Jennifer K. Dick Lilith Crown Quarto, 176pp, €15, Autumn 2019 ISBN 979-10-90394-63-6 Made of gathered dust and the poet’s fine attention, made of making itself, recovered in the marked acts of dreaming and writing, a powerful and transformative feminine figure emerges in Jennifer K. Dick’s latest collection. Bleeding through the veil of ripped wallpaper that haunted Charlotte Perkins Gilman, brilliantly imagined out of stain and shadow into sensual life, this at once contemporary and mythic woman becomes our avatar and intimate: “Lili.” Both an “invitation to see” and, literally, a vision, the result of “rough loving” and splendid—hybrid—writing, Lili is a glorious “cast” (think sculpture, yes, but also outcast and cast of characters, and do keep in mind Mallarmé’s cast of the dice…). Complicating and expanding ideas about identity and femininity, subject and object, novel and verse, Lilith is this poet’s most amazing wager and work. Laura Mullen Jennifer K. Dick Lilithis a plunge of variance—columns, clusters, superscripts, blocks of plot—that delivers its heroin(e) to and from a self. In the woods or in a room of broken porcelain, Lili basks in neuroinformation and Narcissus, getting away from getting away. “Recoil is to leap as harmony is to nail”: this book’s beautiful movement goes everywhere into fragmentation. A fluent multiplicity from Dick’s world-rend(er)ing imaginations. Lisa Samuels Lilith. A Novel in Fragments. Etymology of “novel”—“fictitious narrative,” 1560s, from Italian novella “short story,” originally “new story,” from Latin novella “new things”…. If we are to have a feminist poetics, a feminist poetry, that will have to be a “new thing.” And new things are notoriously difficult to recognize and interpret. Jennifer K. Dick’s newest (in every sense of the word) book challenges us on every level: within the first few pages, we are confronted with scattered words on the page, an overprinted graphic, a phrase printed upside down…. This book is an enormous (perhaps endless) journey, and, like all great journeys, includes elements of circularity, of reimaging, reimagining. We wander in a labyrinth of mirrors, seeing ourselves in these repeated, fragmentary stories, and in the deep and complex eroticism of this text. This is a book that resists summary or description. Like all real novels, it wants to and succeeds in including everything, especially moments of astonishingly lyrical writing: As now, on the bed, a feather, pages. This book is an event. It isn’t about anything. It is something. Ed Smallfield Video: the author reads from Lilith. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Lilith</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/limitedesir.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Meghan McNealy limite désir A5, 28pp, May 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-22-3 The cover image is by the author : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>limite désir</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/longplayep.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : steven dalachinsky long play e.p. the complete Evan Parker Poems A5, 40pp, September 2011, €5 ISBN 979-10-90394-07-0 The cover image is by the author. Poetry & Jazz: possibly the most truly autochthonous North American art combo. Both a high & a popular tradition, way too neglected by the high literati & their low theory–pundits as a formal & spontaneous process that happens “inside / the skillside of the skull”—as the amazing Steven Dalachinsky has it in this lovely, lovely book, a set of poems that sets him squarely (hiply?) in a line starting (in my book) with Kenneth Rexroth & culminating today with, well, maestro Dalachin– sky, an unequaled delight, a must. Pierre Joris If the definition of the “true” poet is someone who translates events around him into words AS THEY HAPPEN, then Steve Dalachinsky is one of the few I know—I“ve seen him scribble a poem on a scrap of paper at a viewing—and if that definition is widened to include being BORN with the natural rhythms of the Universe, the MUSIC OF LIFE, in yr veins, and then being able to infuse yr work with this music, then Steve is the only true poet I know. Ron Kolm, author of The Plastic Factory, editor of The Worst Book I Ever Read Steve Dalachinsky has understood the wish made by John Coltrane of a multi– directional expression: what he hears in the music (of Evan Parker, this time) is nothing less than the realm of possibilities, possible images, possible ideas, possible meanings. You, the readers, are invited to the wedding party of chaos and cosmos. Alexandre Pierrepont, dreamer, poet, surrealist, anthropologist : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>long play e.p.</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/lowlevelflying.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : John Kliphan LOW LEVEL FLYING US Trade, 148pp, €12, March 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-31-5 The cover image is by Peter Cunningham. Published posthumously for John Kliphan’s wake. John Kliphan (b.1933, Boston – d. 2012, Paris) was a passionate and compassionate poet, teacher and lawyer. His poems are direct in approach, accessible yet incisive, lyrical by nature and often humorous. First published in Boston, then San Francisco, where he lived for many years, he befriended the Beats and was counsel for the North Beach art community. In the 1980’s Kliphan moved to Paris, where he founded and directed the Live Poets Society, an internationally recognized series of readings celebrating the oral tradition of poetry while providing a venue for new voices and verse in Paris, the city’s longest–running series of its kind. Invited to perform his work at poetry readings around the world, Kliphan was author of three books of poetry as well as individual poems and various articles published in the United States and Europe. Jennifer Pinard : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>LOW LEVEL FLYING</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/m.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Lily Robert-Foley m Limited Edition US Trade, 266pp, €18, May 2013 ISBN 979-10-90394-14-8 The cover image is by dylan harris. Corrupt Press acknowledges the kind permission of both Faber & Faber and LES EDITIONS DE MINUIT S.A. to collage The Unnamable / Poèmes — collages à partir de L’Innommable : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>m</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/mammals.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Pearl Pirie Mammals of Hoarfrost A5, 28pp, September 2011, €5 ISBN 979-10-90394-16-2 The cover image is “Handala” by the author. Little dense vowel codes per line accrue to wowza table-risk song! Phil Hall She’s quirky, humorous, compassionate, clear-seeing, and she always finds the most interesting conjunctions of words to convey an essence. Rosemary Nissen-Wade Pirie’s poetry will be of interest to anyone who enjoys good wordplay, linguistic gymnastics, humour and surprising twists and turns. Amanda Earl, Ottawa Sneezers : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Mammals of Hoarfrost</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/misscanada.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Rob McLennan Miss Canada A5, 28pp, €5, July 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-31-5 The cover image is by dylan harris. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Miss Canada</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/onecolumbusleap.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Anamaría Crowe Serrano one columbus leap A5, 28pp, September 2011, €5 ISBN 979-10-90394-04-9 The cover image is “Pieces of the Heart” Typesetting by Meghan McNealy Anamaría Crowe Serrano’s one columbus leap is a poetic tour de force on the gestation of Columbus’ 1492 step from the harbour town of Palos de la Frontera to the new world. Her poetry stimulates with linguistic inventiveness and a precise and exhilarating vocabulary that carries the reader far beyond the brooding narrative. It ignites and sparkles on every page with the full range of an energetic and exciting poet on display. This is contemporary poetry at its best. David Caddy, editor of Tears in the Fence. Words in Anamaría Crowe Serrano’s one columbus leap have texture that travel un- der the skin and in between worlds. Their leap is elliptical and their eyes are restless in collecting experience. Things are half-revealed and mystery mists the scenery. There is an insatiable hunger for natural phenomena and a calling for the accuracy of words. Words dance, words create families, alliterations, lists, shapes, labyrinths. Then for a moment: immobility. Whatever is experienced travels deep, establishing new ground. Change is slow and yet again it happens rapidly. Your senses will be initiated here and unexpected occurrences will put you in a spell. This collection is thoroughly recommended. Nina Karacosta, author of Previous Vertigos. Weaving poetry and short prose, one columbus leap fascinates as it evokes a human being progressing toward a “never” that “awaits”. At once vividly precise and full of unsettling metaphorical resonance, Anamaría Crowe Serrano’s sequence sails be- yond the year 1492 and the discoverer of the New World; it lands amid startling natural profusion, but also illness and lucre: it encounters us. John Taylor, author of Into the Heart of European Poetry. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>one columbus leap</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/orantes.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : William J. Doan orantes linguis A5, 28pp, €5, November 2011 ISBN 979-10-90394-18-6 The cover image is by dylan harris. What a devious bit of writing. Doan’s poems remind me of both Finnegan’s Wake and the Simpsons—they gnaw at the emptied hope found in double wide debt, class realities, brutish fathers and unscrupulous bankers. The familiar chanted rhythm of prayer is a frayed nylon fire rope for all confined to the dictated lives of their class. Helen O’Leary, Guggenheim Fellow, 2010 In orantes linguis, Bill Doan draws power out of paradoxes: Catholicism, obedience, and poverty coexist with subversiveness and resistance. We are haunted by the memory of the fidgety friend who died in childhood; we can feel the marks on the body left by the nun and the stepfather. Doan’s voice can be incantatory about the condition of being broken, even as it surprises us with humor and the possibility of healing. Readers will come away from this work convinced—to paraphrase Jerome McGann—that poetry is a form of social action. Nancy Locke, art historian, author of Manet and the Family Romance William Doan’s orantes linguis is amazing in every sense of the word. Linguistically kinetic and full of twisted humor, it’s as if Joyce’s “Portrait of the Artist as a Young Man” and Frank O’Hara’s paens to the everyday had birthed a child. But Doan’s voice is also entirely his own. Down to earth yet transcendent, raw yet incandescent, this book gets to the heart of Catholicism and childhood, excavating memory and existence with precision and genuine insight. The end result is dazzling. To paraphrase a line from Doan himself, ’this book is incantatory.’ Alistair McCartney, author of The End of the World Book: A Novel. William Doan’s orantes linguis is a charged soundscape of how growing up rural, Catholic and working class rings in his ears—the stinging “thwack” and “ping” of it. The work is so wise and soul-full of the way family hurt and hope breathes in him each day. Bravely claiming the “tongue” in the title, this moving work from William Doan finds a new voice, a deeper prayer to remember who he comes from and to chart where he is going. Tim Miller, performer and author of Shirts & Skin Bill Doan’s writing here holds memory close to the blood and bone, ringing fugue-like in consciousness the way a song or a smell can echo us straight back into childhood, bypassing caution. The high-stakes world of these poetic dramas—populated by lawnmowers, dirty carpets, alcoholic stepfathers, and the heavy weather of Christianity—linger as the dirty, little parables that know the secret paradoxes of a rural American boyhood. This is writing as an act of unflinching spiritual longing. Andrew Belser, Chair, Department of Theatre, University of North Carolina Wilmington : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>orantes linguis</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/organspeech.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Megan Fernandes Organ Speech A5, 40pp, €5, November 2011 ISBN 979-10-90394-10-0 The cover image is by Joshua Neves and Graham Bury. It is exciting to discover a new poet and a new press. Megan Fernandes is a sophisticated and sensitive writer, and her poems are, by turn, surprising, vivid and affecting. Organ Speech is unnervingly good. Read more of Charles Whalley’s piece in Sabotage Reviews. From Megan Fernandes you can learn that language has an energy of its own, much like the (Kinetics) of a pink leaf, running somehow parallel to us, able sometimes to be spooned up & turned over, like the air, or different coloured light, in the hands of only the very carefulest listeners and observers—like Fernandes. You can learn how adjectives are palpable as meat and why young women cheat and about pennies from Yeats’ poems. You can learn what queens do with little boys behind blue-rutted buses; about dinosaurs & neurons and the catastrophe of gestures. You can learn about the soft anger of the poet & certain other overlooked corners of the brain; about movement & food stuffs & ontologies & joy. She can teach you all this. Emily Critchley Neurons, synapses, matter, planets and energy describe memories and their relation to the present tense. ‘The sounds grows.’ Imagine a poetry that anthropomorphises cellular process, that excavates the operations beneath ontology, which is philosophy, which is a body in motion, sense organs all open: this is that. Organ Speech is provocative, lyrical, suspenseful, exciting, sexy, and full of ideas. TOUCH EVERYTHING Marianne Morris : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Organ Speech</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/parted.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : justina semetaite Parted A5, 28pp, €5, November 2011 ISBN 979-10-90394-23-0 The cover image is a detail from Boat by Migle Semetaite. why have we not heard of Justina Semetaite until now? with Parted this wrong will be corrected. when she talks to herself about good-byes “The garden is empty, or is it my eyes?” when she writes postcards “Through your white, glossy moss.” when in the long powerful closing poem “maybe the blossoms of books, maybe the sound of trees, maybe the wall, greeting an old woman’s flickers.” this is just the beginning, right? lars palm, author of road song for From the opening lines of Justina Semetaite’s Parted, “The jelly shadows of the birds / sitting on the fence,” we know we are in good poetic company: the kind that’s able to think laterally about language, treat it as the physical stuff that it is, whilst also working it lyrically, languidly, in a book as private yet communal as singing the national anthem (but which one? ). -—so good to be back—- such a sadness / a mouthful of mustard Semetaite’s zeugma (are birds on the fence or just their jelly shadows?) and other happy language disruptions (choosing an ‘of’ in place of a ‘to’ because it sounds & means better) are proof if any were needed that being ‘between’ languages can be a definite advantage. Her idiosyncratic metaphors are fresh as drunk energy, her sounds satisfying as the “pop of a stranger’s umbrella”. Emily Critchley, author of ImaginaryLovePoems : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Parted</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/peneloping.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Amy Hollowell Peneloping A5, 32pp, €5, November 2011 ISBN 979-10-90394-19-3 The cover image is Constellation 2 (oil on canvas). Peneloping is a beautiful energy construct of poems calling to mind’s ear both the participial glee of Gertrude Stein’s “continuous present” and the verbal shapeshifting of James Joyce. Antics and intricate care: “bespun and bespanning/allhere/and beshifting”. Kudos to Amy Hollowell’s exuberant and special measure. Anne Waldman, author of Fast Speaking Woman : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Peneloping</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/previous.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Nina Karacosta Previous Vertigos A5, 24pp, February 2011, €5 ISBN 979-10-90394-01-8 The cover image is “Compasses And The Elastic Eye”, by the author. Le traduction en français, par Anne Talvaz, est Vertiges Précédents. The vertigo in the title of Nina Karacosta’s Previous Vertigos’s draws attention to a whirling or spinning movement, to the causes and history of that motion and the narrator’s attitudes to those movements. Poems flicker and wobble in the collection. They situate the vertigo within relationships and the narrative search for an adequate response to a specific dizziness by finding a form for each instance. This produces an inventive openness to self, self and others, to self and place and to self and the ground upon which she walks. The self is not always stationary but rather seen in suspension or truncation. It is this openness to the vagaries of the self and its relations and in disturbance to dizzying motion, most graphically in poems such as ‘Can’t Talk About It’, ‘The Story Of Everything’, ‘Psychotropic Hurrah’ and ‘Under’ that makes this collection such a cracking read. I thoroughly recommend this collection. David Caddy, editor of Tears in the Fence Karacosta’s imagery is often exotic, with orchids and hummingbirds, peyote and spices, but these are counterbalanced with altogether more biological terms: photosphere, embroid, analgetic membranes, mitochondria, fluid flesh. Here is a poet who aims to subvert our expectations at every turn. The result is a kind of schizophrenia that is intriguing. Read Afric McGlinchey’s full review at Sabotage Reviews. Previous Vertigos is a collection of memories, advice to self, and reflections captured in windows. Nina Karacosta’s first collection is mysteriously original; told through a megaphone. The voice of a very wise underground soul cascading through the rugged cliffs on a distant seascape. Oddly, this voice is so fresh, so recently acquired, it’s as if the speaker is telling herself this ancient advice for the very first time. There is a power here, which at times seems to startle the speaker. “i can maybe write a pow wow poem”. Reading these poems is like reading a Tarot spread: there is a lot going on but if you look closer there is even more going on and everything seems to be telling you about this very moment. An awareness that isn’t logical. A travelling through time and space on a bus that never leaves the station. Scaling the walls of the interior. Harsh chchbit rapid call in the glass palaces of your childhood where he whispers his yellow skin on horizontal branches of tree. This is a meditation on letting go of the past and capturing the hidden mysteries of all the previousness. An attempt at isolating it in order to learn from it. Talk back to it. Karacosta has a keen sense for the dreamy. These poems dig down and burrow. They are naturally occurring. “I had crystals hidden into my earth. / I was a crow.” Things are definitely not what they appear to be; unraveling and unraveling like “worn out legs / away from summer.” Susanna Fry : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Previous Vertigos</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/roadkill.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Michelle Noteboom Roadkill US Trade, 84pp, €12, July 2013 ISBN 979-10-90394-11-7 The cover design is by Frédéric Forte using an image by Daniel Levin Becker. Making the most of a collision of dictions, on the one hand, while spanning era, class, and mood on the other, Noteboom sails directly and fearlessly into the quotidian—yet with an astronomical dimension. This collection is fueled by a recogni- tion of the great range that language can cover, and that it can create. Often irreverent and almost always sassy, Noteboom’s texts make language travel at tremendous speed, and she’s an excellent chronicler of every inch of territory she makes it cover. It’s a startling and marvellous ride! Cole Swensen This is one roadkill that simply refuses to stay down. A book that shows the vapidness of our daily monotony colliding head-on with unfilled desires and yearnings to be whole and happy; and the obviously laughable impossibility of just that given our fractured society. “Can we blame this on Capitalism, too?” Noteboom asks. Good question. Even a better read. Roadkill leaves plenty of room for the reader to confront and ponder, and have a good belly laugh or two during the trip. Joe Ross : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Roadkill</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/roadsong.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : lars palm road song for US Trade, 100pp, €12, September 2011 ISBN 979-10-90394-12-4 The cover image is by Petra Palm In the concise verses and prose poems of road song for, Lars Palm reminds us–as he always does–of the music of everyday English, from overheard conversations to pop lyrics. Often light in tone but never slight, Palm’s work is carefully built to look effortless. — Amanda Laughtland This is a wonderful book of impulsive and magical, lyrical poetry. — Robert Loydell, Stride Magazine. D e p r e s s u r e placement is in a sociocultural and sociogeographic sense poetry; oncesilence.gov: as every twig snapped; as non-equivalence: delusions are a wonderful tool for all manner of artists, whom are subject to Lars Palm, who often use them to cast a clearer light on reality; and reality this is, what comes after this, is [ repeat ] — Freke Räihä Inte honungssött direkt men mättande och närande likaså — not dripping with honey but filling & nourishing as well — Albert Herranz : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>road song for</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/sc.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : George Vance A SHORT CIRCUIT A4, 96pp, €12, May 2011 ISBN 979-10-90394-00-1 The cover image is by the author. To have so much of the collected work of George Vance under one cover is a real treat. I’ve been reading Vance’s poetry for almost two decades. His word fugues and constructs are smart, witty, full of graceful aperçus, and challenging. Read them once, read them twice—never the same river. J. Sydney Jones, author of Viennese Mysteries godzilla’sinheaven, and here below are poems fiddling dancing dazzling drizzling in black and white, all senses contend before our eyes, spinfoam gossamer, tree-suns’ threesomes (not treason), sentences that require attention. Look closely: Sometimes after smiles, intimacies lurk to creep into our minds. Sir Real, George Vance, is a wondrous one-man Word Ensemble of Paris. John Litweiler, author of Mojo Snake Minuet A lot of contemporary poetry is uninteresting, uninviting, unreadable. This cannot be said of A Short Circuit. It’s exciting! Gabriel Rosenstock : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>A SHORT CIRCUIT</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/shelf.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : rufo quintavalle Shelf 1–15 In English and French, traduit de l’anglais par Ian Monk A5, 40pp, €8, October 2015 ISBN 979-10-90394-54-4 The cover image is by dylan harris. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Shelf 1–15</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/shipfur.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : James Jewell Ships Made of Fake Fur A5, 24pp, €4, January 2013 ISBN 979-10-90394-38-4 The cover image is by the author : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Ships Made of Fake Fur</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/silentg.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Arpine Konyalian Grenier The Silent G US Trade, 81pp, €15, 2019 ISBN 979-10-90394-60-5 The cover image is by dylan harris Dislocated in time and space, these words turn longing into flesh as they haunt memory with images both bitter and sweet–poems to read and reread and to ponder what history has made of us, and what we will make of it. A diasporic masterpiece. Stephen K Levine The way she puts it… “that was the killer, that poetry. You pulled the covers over you and your poetry, then found a stranger right there, under the covers with you.”… is exactly right, that’s what poetry does, because it is itself, unbeknownst to you, that stranger you try to hide from under those covers. Go find it — read this book! Pierre Joris The conceded weave of memory into poetry, with history and the art of the poem, all this surfaces like magnificent sea beasts breaking the plane of the water, all that was underneath now is here fixed, rising as the stars, moon, and in sun silence loud. Michael Basinski : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>The Silent G</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/skypp.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Sarah Chapman Sky + + A5, 28pp, €6, September 2014 ISBN 979-10-90394-49-0 The cover image is by the author. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Sky + +</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/standardform.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Freke Räihä Standard Form for Language Resentment US Trade, 64pp, €12, April 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-26-1 Translated from Swedish by the author. The cover image is by dylan harris. Hear Freke read from his work. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Standard Form for Language Resentment</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/stonebride.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Nicolette Wong Stone Bride Madrigals A5, 28pp, €6, December 2013 ISBN 979-10-90394-44-5 The cover image is by David Heg : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Stone Bride Madrigals</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/stwah.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : reuben woolley some time we are heroes US Trade, 81pp, €15, September 2018 ISBN 979-10-90394-58-2 The cover image is by Jan Stead Reuben Woolley’s some time we are heroes traces the frayed relationship between two people in terms of a despairing yet lyrical crisis. Images of water, dancing, drinking and singing run through the book in poems whose lines shift nervously to produce a kind of sharp–edged jazz that touches both nerve and heart. George Szirtes John and Mary, whose trials began in children’s post–war picture books, are pitched into existential tribulations in a dystopian universe, akin to Popa’s. These poems occupy the worlds of both myth and physics with flashes of folk–surrealism. Woolley’s language is spare, his syntax and word–choice paint an off–kilter logic. His use of white space allows the poems, and their imaginative journeys, to perform themselves on the page. Helen Ivory In a line with our most ambitious striving for a new poetry and poetics, Woolley’s poems are both innovative in their means and open to the ruptures & struggles of our time that have broken apart the stories & myths that once held our world together — or that purported to do so. The results here are unique to his own special view of history & masterfully compelling. Jerome Rothenberg I commend to you this stylistically distinctive collection of poems where the universality of human relationships is, among many moving impressions, a haunting as well as affirming exploration. Mike Ferguson, mikeandenglish blog : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>some time we are heroes</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/suspension.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Pansy Maurer-Alvarez IN A FORM OF SUSPENSION US Trade, 64pp, €15, April 2014 ISBN 979-10-90394-46-9 The cover image is by dylan harris. Poets have often been the patsies for a predetermined set of truths, even as love, joy, safety, and sanctity rarely resemble what they’re purported to be. Poets become reduced to intellectualism and academicism—their truths provincially categorized before they’ve been written. When these constraints prove insufficient, a poet may only have her own instincts to rely on. In her new book, IN A FORM OF SUSPENSION, Pansy Maurer-Alvarez forgoes prescribed meaning, favoring her sonic palette as a guide to the pleasures of poetry. These are passionate poems, “authentically uncertain,” where “late temperate nature echoes revelations.” These poems inhabit a space of wild observation, offering moments of fused-grammar joy (“mimosa is composed of Seville”), but grounded by a delight in physicality. “I wanted to unleash brash themes, I wanted their warped gleam to hold me cleft to my own light,” she writes. Joy, social detail, a love for language, an urban wit, all combine in this book into an ”invisible room …grazed by pale orbs of song.“ Edmund Berrigan IN A FORM OF SUSPENSION is a lush, erotic book that presents the reader with the amorous wardrobe of being. Feminine, incisive, capricious, and analytical, the poems move the reader with their throbbing pulsations, and cool lacunas. Distortion, sound clusters, and a slight aura of La Belle Époque color the poems. Maurer-Alvarez uses cacophony as a structuring principle; the clattering of sound creates momentum; the breaking down of sound clusters reduces the heaviness of language and allows the reader to participate in the deconstruction of connectivity. The main theme of romanticism externalized and defused becomes the central reference point of the poems. The tension between the often-bleak reality beyond the self and its intimacy fades from time to time. The poet then speaks in a clear personal voice; the “bare literary figurine” becomes a mature woman reflecting on her life, on sexuality, on presence, and the immense potential of language to liberate and redefine the human spirit. Andrea Moorhead : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>IN A FORM OF SUSPENSION</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/thesunbrings.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Christophe Lamiot Enos The Sun Brings US Trade, 120pp, €12, May 2013 ISBN 979-10-90394-39-1 The cover image is reproduced courtesy of the author. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>The Sun Brings</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/trialballoons.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Alexander Dickow Trial Balloons A5, 36pp, €5, June 2012 Reprinted September 2015 ISBN 979-10-90394-36-0 The cover image is by an unknown artist. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Trial Balloons</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/turnpush.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : kit fryatt turn push | turn pull A5, 28pp, €5, August 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-33-9 The cover image is turn push | turn pull by Andrej Kapor. Fryatt has something to compress here, so that it isn’t clipped, not the manner of a clipped or withdrawn person, but a jump cut and besuited highwire full army kit suspension of a dance floor in midair. Ira Lightman turn push | turn pull is a celebration of the form and function of words, their morphologies and etymologies, how they convey meaning and simultaneously defy it. Eloquent as always, with Socratic wisdom and an ear that is sensitively attuned to the push/pull of cadence, Fryatt prods and carefully dissects the word while she muses on love, friendship, consciousness. Her wit is on every page, even in the silences. She thrills the reader with meticulous reinvention and the gliss of regional variations, tucking foreign phrases with their English fellows to create a voice that is multi-layered and infinitely rewarding. Anamaría Crowe Serrano : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>turn push | turn pull</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/tweet.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about &cir; authors &cir; books &cir; submissions &cir; view cart : : Greg Santos Tweet Tweet Tweet A5, 32pp inc. colour, &euro;8, December 2011 ISBN 979-10-90394-24-7 With Tweet Tweet Tweet, Santos has created a world both elegiac and exuberant, where &ldquo;wind-up owls whirr incessantly&rdquo; and poets are &ldquo;endlessly sculpting birds out of words.&rdquo; Funny, sincere, and self-aware, these are the poems of our moment and its changing modes of reality and connection. A collection of &ldquo;exquisite topiaries,&rdquo; disarming and affecting. Paula Bohince, author of Incident at the Edge of Bayonet Woods : : contact &cir; terms of use &cir; privacy & cookies &cir; terms of sale &cir; returns &cir; delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press &cir; © 2011&ndash;2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Tweet Tweet Tweet</title>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/understory.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Rod Mengham The Understory A6, 28pp, €6, February 2014 ISBN 979-10-90394-47-6 The cover image is by John Gibbons : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>The Understory</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/verisimilitude.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Suzanne Allen Verisimilitude A5, 24pp, €5 First edition June 2011 Second edition May 2014 ISBN 979-10-90394-05-6 The cover image is by dylan harris. Typesetting by Meghan McNealy. Verisimilitude is the debut pamphlet of Suzanne Allen, a regular on the Anglophone Parisian scene. Published by the equally Paris-based Corrupt Press, it is a modest-looking yet beautiful collection, with an evocative cover of a rundown interior. I first encountered Allen’s poetry when she gave a performance of her long poem ‘Wail’ (anthologized in Not a Muse: the inner lives of women) a feminist retelling of Ginsberg’s ‘Howl’ at Culture Rapide. While the poem does not feature in this pamphlet, the short opening poem ‘(un)loaded’ feels very much in the same vein, a call for inclusion: ‘There’s a (w)hole in my can(n)on where a (wo)man should be.’ This poem perhaps best summarizes the pamphlet: a questioning of language and of status quo, through humour and heart. Verisimilitude is a collection of love, of loneliness, and the pursuit to palliate the latter through an exploration of language. Claire Trevien, Sabotage Reviews. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Verisimilitude</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/vertiges.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Nina Karacosta Vertiges Précédents Traduction au français, par Anne Talvaz, de Previous Vertigos A5, 28pp, €5, Janvier 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-25-4 : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Vertiges Précédents</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/weak.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : R L Raymond Weakdays A5, 32pp, €5, July 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-37-8 The cover image is by the author. Hear Wolfgang Carstens read five poems from Weakdays. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Weakdays</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/wolfdown.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : Anthony Liccione Wolf Down US Trade, 84pp, €12, December 2011 ISBN 979-10-90394-20-9 The cover image is Wolf Eat WolfMagnhild Opdøl View a video of Illusion, a poem from the book. Knowing what“s out there in the world doesn“t mean you also have to let it destroy you. The good is taken with the bad in Wolf Down, and the transition from one to the other is seamless, and the mark of a writer as tired yet willing and eager to continue on. It is the gratitude of still being alive, coming through the minor and severe hells of an ordinary day more or less intact. It is not something easily gained in life, but it“s always worth trying for. The writer capable of telling us of their journey through this as well as Liccione will never lack for material. When the material is as good as that which is found in Wolf Down we gain almost as much as he does. Just by reading what’s on his mind. Gabriel Ricard, Unlikely Blog The first indication of what to expect in Anthony Liccione“s Wolf Down is his biography on the back. The bio is a grim and sobering reminder of the kind of hard knocks life can deliver and his poems follow the same trajectory: raw, dark, and unforgiving. Wolf Down“s template is the dull, routine, and unflattering part of life. But what gives this book its edge is Liccione“s poetic skill, which lies in his ability to deftly lift scenarios out of the ordinary and stain them with gloom. He hops from news stories turned tragic in One to distasteful corners of society in The Dance of Ignorance, delivering his poems with an unflinching, surgical eye. “As I write,” he says in Starvation, again “the world grows uglier…” The world“s ugliness, no doubt, has informed Liccione“s style and he serves it up cold: in death beds and at the back of police cars. He paints domesticity as a sort of grim banality (What tomorrow may bring); treats domestic violence with disturbing routine (Coping with cops, that drive with a dozen donuts on the front seat); and allows us to be a fly on the wall as a man receives his medical death sentence (Bad news, too soon). Bleak, yes. But in dark holes, there’s that occasional light. And in Wolf Down, poems like Sense of freedom remind us that sparks of happiness can exist even within the darkest of writers. Underground Voices : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>Wolf Down</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/books/xmas.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : George Vance XMAS COLLAGE A5, 28pp, June 2012 ISBN 979-10-90394-32-2 The cover image is by the author : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>XMAS COLLAGE</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>buy,for sale,poetry,book,print</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/index.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : publisher’s books : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>corrupt press</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press puts poetry in peoples&rsquo; heads</description>
<keywords>poetry,publisher,books</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/info/about.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : corrupt press about When I moved to Paris in December 2009, I found many interesting anglophone poets, a lively scene, magazines, but no small press. Worse, some British, Irish and American poetry presses seemed unwilling to publish poets from their abroad. In consequence, good poets weren’t getting published. So, in 2011, I set corrupt press up. In 2012, I moved it to Scotland, where I incorporated it as a limited company. However, the limited company was abandoned in 2016 because of Brexit. Corrupt Press is now, like me, based in Luxembourg. Non–anglophone English can be an interesting source of new language. The poetry may sometimes seem odd to native speakers, but is it error, a style that’s not yet established, a different grammar, an effect a native speaker would struggle to achieve, or what? That’s why I want poetry from poets whose mother tongues exclude English. Those poetry sects, civil warriors lobbing creosotic grenades, farting in general directions: I don’t care for them. I do care for interesting poetry, high quality poetry, from anywhere. I do care for different poetry, doing things well I’ve not seen done before. I do care for traditional poetry, doing the same again, very well indeed. I want to be excited by poetry, and I don’t care if it’s Stockhausen or stuck. Books are tools for putting poems into heads. It’s the poetry, not the tool, so corrupt press books are simple. No tool is perfect; books lose sound, speech loses sight, ebooks need fuel. Corrupt press is considering other tools, but want to get it right—right for putting poems in heads, right as business practice. You can contact the press at dh@corruptpress.com. dylan harris April 2019 : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>about corrupt press</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>corrupt press poetry publisher luxembourg esch-sur-alzette english</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/info/cart.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : view cart This page will vamoosh once I’ve worked out how to link the paypal cart directly from a text menu item. In the meantime, to view your cart, please click the button below. Apologies for the complication. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>view cart</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>Link to view your shopping cart from corrupt press.</description>
<keywords>Link to view your shopping cart from corrupt press.</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/info/delivery.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : corrupt press delivery policy Introduction This policy contains details of the delivery methods, periods and charges that apply to orders for our products made through our website or by telephone or email. This policy does not create legally enforceable rights and obligations; it merely indicates our usual practice in relation to the delivery of products. Free delivery We offer free standard delivery to all addresses on all orders of €50 or more. All other orders will be subject to delivery charges as detailed in Section 5. Geographical limitations We will usually be able to deliver to all countries and territories in the European Economic Area, North America, Australia and New Zealand. We may from time to time agree to delivery products to other countries and territories. Delivery methods and periods The methods that we use to deliver our products, and the time periods within which delivery is usually completed, are those specified by Post Luxembourg. If you place your order before 4pm on a working day, these time periods run from the close of business on that day; if you place your order after 4pm on a working day, or on a non–working day, these time periods run from the close of business on the next following working day. The delivery periods set out in this Section 4 are indicative only, and whilst we will make every effort to ensure that you receive your delivery in good time, we do not guarantee delivery before the end of the stated period. We may conduct fraud screening checks before dispatching the product, and these checks may delay your delivery. If the delivery is likely to be delayed as a result of fraud screening checks, we will notify you. Delivery charges Delivery charges will be calculated by our website and automatically applied to your order during the checkout process, or alternatively quoted by us. Applicable delivery charges will depend upon the value of the products in your order. Our delivery charges are as follows: €4 for an order of less that €10; free for an order of €50 or more; and €9 otherwise. Delivery tracking Delivery tracking is available when provided by Post Luxembourg. To track your delivery, enter your order number (which is provided in your delivery information email) into our delivery service provider’s website here: http://www.trackandtrace.lu/. Receipt and signature Tracked deliveries must be received in person at the delivery address, and a signature must be provided. Our delivery service provider may notify you in advance of attempting to make a delivery requiring signature. Additional deliveries If an initial delivery attempt is unsuccessful, our delivery service provider may make at least 1 more attempt to deliver the products in your order. Collection If your products remain undelivered despite our delivery service provider making an attempt to deliver them, the delivery service provider will leave a card at your address, with instructions on how you may collect your products, including a time limit for collection. Delivery problems If you experience any problems with a delivery, please contact us using the contact details that we publish on our website or otherwise notify to you. If our delivery service provider is unable to deliver your products, and such failure is your fault, and you do not collect your products from our delivery service provider within the relevant time limit, we may agree to arrange for re–delivery of the products; however, we reserve the right to charge you for the actual costs of re–delivery (even where the initial delivery was free of charge). An indicative list of the situations where a failure to deliver will be your fault is set out below: you provided the wrong address for delivery; there is a mistake in the address for delivery that was provided; the address for delivery is not reasonably accessible; the address for delivery cannot safely be accessed; if in–person receipt is not required, there is no easy and secure means of leaving the products at the address for delivery and there is no person available to accept delivery; or if in–person receipt is required, there is no person available at the address for delivery to accept delivery and provide a signature. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>delivery policy</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>corrupt press poetry publisher luxembourg esch-sur-alzette english</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/info/privacy.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : corrupt press privacy and cookies policies Part 1: Personal information and privacy Introduction We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information. By using our website and agreeing to this policy, you consent to our use of cookies in accordance with the terms of this policy. Collecting personal information We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal information: information about your computer and about your visits to and use of this website (including but not limited to your IP address, geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths); information that you provide to us for the purpose of subscribing to our email notifications and/or newsletters; information relating to any purchases you make of our goods (including your name, delivery address, payment address, telephone numbers, and email address); information contained in or relating to any communications that you send to us (including the communication content and meta data associated with the communication); and any other personal information that you choose to send to us. Before you disclose to us the personal information of another person, you must obtain that person’s consent to both the disclosure and the processing of that personal information in accordance with the terms of this policy. Using your personal information Personal information submitted to us through our website will be used for the purposes specified in this policy or on the relevant pages of the website. We may use your personal information to: administer our website and business; personalise our website for you; enable your use of the services available on our website; send you goods purchased through our website; send statements, invoices and payment reminders to you, and collect payments from you; send you non–marketing commercial communications; send you email notifications that you have specifically requested; send you our email newsletter, if you have requested it (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require the newsletter); send you marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully–selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you, by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology (you can inform us at any time if you no longer require marketing communications); provide third parties with statistical information about our users (but those third parties will not be able to identify any individual user from that information); deal with enquiries and complaints made by or about you relating to our website; keep our website secure and prevent fraud; verify compliance with the terms and conditions governing the use of our website; and any other uses. If you submit personal information for publication on our website, we will publish and otherwise use that information in accordance with the licence you grant to us. We will not, without your express consent, supply your personal information to any third party for the purpose of their or any other third party’s direct marketing. All our website financial transactions are handled through our payment services provider, paypal. You can review the provider’s privacy policy at https://www.paypal.com/. We will share information with our payment services provider only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our website, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. Disclosing personal information We may disclose your personal information to any of our employees, officers, insurers, professional advisers, agents, suppliers or subcontractors insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy. We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group of companies (this means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries) insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this policy. We may disclose your personal information: to the extent that we are required to do so by law; in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings; in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); to the purchaser (or prospective purchaser) of any business or asset that we are (or are contemplating) selling; and to any person who we reasonably believe may apply to a court or other competent authority for disclosure of that personal information where, in our reasonable opinion, such court or authority would be reasonably likely to order disclosure of that personal information. Except as provided in this policy, we will not provide your personal information to third parties. International data transfers Information that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to enable us to use the information in accordance with this policy. Information that we collect may be transferred to the following countries which do not have data protection laws equivalent to those in force in the European Economic Area: the United States of America, Russia, Japan, China and India. Personal information that you publish on our website or submit for publication on our website may be available, via the internet, around the world. We cannot prevent the use or misuse of such information by others. You expressly agree to the transfers of personal information described in this section. Retaining personal information This section sets out our data retention policies and procedure, which are designed to help ensure that we comply with our legal obligations in relation to the retention and deletion of personal information. Personal information that we process for any purpose or purposes shall not be kept for longer than is necessary for that purpose or those purposes. Notwithstanding the other provisions of this section, we will retain documents (including electronic documents) containing personal data: to the extent that we are required to do so by law; if we believe that the documents may be relevant to any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings; and in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk). Security of your personal information We will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure (password– and firewall–protected) servers. All electronic financial transactions entered into through our website will be protected by encryption technology. You acknowledge that the transmission of information over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet. You are responsible for keeping the password you use for accessing our website confidential; we will not ask you for your password (except when you log in to our website). Amendments We may update this policy from time to time by publishing a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes to this policy. Your rights You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you; provision of such information will be subject to: the payment of a fee (currently fixed at €12); and the supply of appropriate evidence of your identity (for this purpose, we will usually accept a photocopy of your passport certified by a solicitor or bank plus an original copy of a utility bill showing your current address). We may withhold personal information that you request to the extent permitted by law. You may instruct us at any time not to process your personal information for marketing purposes. In practice, you will usually either expressly agree in advance to our use of your personal information for marketing purposes, or we will provide you with an opportunity to opt out of the use of your personal information for marketing purposes. Third party websites Our website includes hyperlinks to, and details of, third party websites. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the privacy policies and practices of third parties. Updating information Please let us know if the personal information that we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. Part 2: Cookies About cookies A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either ‘persistent’ cookies or ‘session’ cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies. Cookies can be used by web servers to identity and track users as they navigate different pages on a website and identify users returning to a website. Our cookies We do not use cookies on our website. We may use other cookies required from time to time by other websites we may use. Analytics cookies We may use Google Analytics to analyse the use of our website. Our analytics service provider generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Our analytics service provider’s privacy policy is available at https://www.google.com/. Third party cookies Our website may use third party cookies. Details of other third party cookies used by our website are set out below: Any cookies used by paypal. Information on these cookies can be found at https://www.paypal.com/. Any other cookies that may be necessary for the correct and efficient functioning of our website. Blocking cookies Blocking all cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites. If you block cookies, you may not be able to use all the features on our website. Deleting cookies You can delete cookies already stored on your computer. Deleting cookies may have a negative impact on the usability of many websites. Part 3: Our details Our details This website is owned and operated by dylan harris; dylan harris lives and works in the luxembourg; You can email corrupt press at dh@corruptpress.com. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>privacy and cookies policies</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>corrupt press poetry publisher luxembourg esch-sur-alzette english</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/info/returns.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : corrupt press returns policy Introduction We understand that from time to time you may wish to return a product to us. We have created this policy to enable you to return products to us in appropriate circumstances. This policy applies to all of our customers, irrespective of their geographical location. This policy applies to all orders submitted through our website. This document does not affect any statutory rights you may have as a consumer. Returns If you have no other legal right to return a product and receive a refund or exchange, then you will nonetheless be entitled to return a product to us and receive a refund in accordance with this policy if: we receive the returned product within 60 days following the date of dispatch of the product to you; the returned product is in a condition enabling us to sell the product as new; you comply with the procedure set out in this policy in relation to the return of the product; and none of the exclusions set out in this policy apply. Returns procedure In order to take advantage of your rights under this policy, you must contact us to obtain a return authorisation number, and then send the product to us with a covering note quoting that number. Products returned under this policy must be returned to an address we specify. You will be responsible for paying postage costs associated with returns under this policy. Exclusions The following kinds of products may not be returned under this policy: DVDs, CDs and other audio or video or audio–visual recordings; computer software (whether on CD–ROM, DVD–ROM or otherwise); newspapers, periodicals, magazines or similar products; any product made to your specification; any product made to order; any product personalised or adapted for you; or gift vouchers. Refunds We will give you a refund for the price you paid to us in respect of any product properly returned by you in accordance with this policy. We will not refund to you the original delivery charges relating to the returned product. We will not refund to you any costs you incur in returning the product to us. We will usually refund any money received from you using the same method originally used by you to pay for your purchase. We will process the refund due to you as soon as possible and, in any event, within 30 days following the day we receive your returned product. Improper returns If you return a product in contravention of this policy, and you do not have any other legal right to a refund or exchange in respect of that product: we will not refund the purchase price or exchange the product; we may retain the returned product until you pay to us such additional amount as we may charge for re–delivery of the returned product; and if we do not receive payment of such additional amount within 14 days of issuing a request for payment, we may destroy or otherwise dispose of the returned product in our sole discretion without any liability to you. Our details This website is owned and operated by dylan harris; dylan harris lives and works in the luxembourg; You can email corrupt press at dh@corruptpress.com. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>returns policy</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>corrupt press poetry publisher luxembourg esch-sur-alzette english</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/info/sale.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : corrupt press terms & conditions of sale Introduction These terms and conditions govern the sale and purchase of products through our website. You will be asked to give your express agreement to these terms and conditions before you place an order on our website. This document does not affect any statutory rights you may have as a consumer. Interpretation In these terms and conditions: “we” means corrupt press; and “you” means our customer or prospective customer, and “us”, “our” and “your” should be construed accordingly. Order process The advertising of products on our website constitutes an ‘invitation to treat’ rather than a contractual offer. No contract will come into force between you and us unless and until we accept your order in accordance with the procedure set out in this Section 3. To enter into a contract through our website to purchase products from us, the following steps must be taken: you must add the products you wish to purchase to your shopping cart, and then proceed to the checkout; you will be transferred to our payment service provider’s website, and our payment service provider will handle your payment; we will then send you an initial acknowledgement; and once we have checked whether we are able to meet your order, we will either send you an order confirmation (at which point your order will become a binding contract) or we will confirm by email that we are unable to meet your order. You will have the opportunity to identify and correct input errors prior to making your order by cancelling and restarting. Products The following types of products are or may be available on our website from time to time: books, CDs, posters and prints. We may periodically change the products available on our website, and we do not undertake to continue to supply any particular product or type of product. Prices The prices of our products are quoted on our website. We will from time to time change the product prices quoted on our website, but this will not affect contracts that have previously come into force. In addition to the price of the products, you will have to pay a delivery charge, which will be notified to you before the contract of sale comes into force. Payments You must, during the checkout process, pay the prices of the products you order. Payments must be made by any of the permitted methods specified on our website from time to time. If you fail to pay to us any amount due under these terms and conditions in accordance with the provisions of these terms and conditions, then we may withhold the products ordered and/or by written notice to you at any time cancel the contract of sale for the products. If you make an unjustified credit card, debit card or other charge–back then you will be liable to pay us, within 7 days following the date of our written request: an amount equal to the amount of the charge-back; all third party expenses incurred by us in relation to the charge–back (including charges made by our or your bank or payment processor or card issuer); an administration fee of €25.00; and all our reasonable costs, losses and expenses incurred in recovering the amounts referred to in this Section 6.4 (including without limitation legal fees and debt collection fees), and for the avoidance of doubt, if you fail to recognise or fail to remember the source of an entry on your card statement or other financial statement, and make a charge–back as a result, this will constitute an unjustified charge–back for the purposes of this Section 6.4. Deliveries Our policies and procedures relating to the delivery of products are set out in our delivery policy document. Distance selling: right of cancellation This section applies if and only if you contract with us as a consumer. Consumers have a right to cancel any distance contract to purchase a product or products from us at any time within the period: beginning upon the conclusion of the contract of sale under these terms and conditions; and ending after a period of 7 working days beginning with the day after the day on which you receive the product or products, subject to the limitations set out in this section. You will not have any right to cancel a contract as described in this section insofar as the contract relates to: the supply of any products which constitute audio or video recordings or computer software which have been unsealed by you; the supply of products the price of which is dependent upon fluctuations in financial markets which we cannot control; the supply of goods made to your specifications or clearly personalised. In order to cancel a contract on the basis described in this section, you must give to us written notice of cancellation, which may be sent to the business address or email address specified on our website. If you cancel a contract on the basis described in this section, you must return the product or products to us. If you cancel a contract on the basis described in this section, you will receive a full refund of the amount you paid, including the cost of sending the product or products to you; however, you will be responsible for paying the cost of returning the product or products to us. If you cancel a contract on the basis described in this section and you do not return the product or products to us, we may recover the product or products and charge you for the costs we incur in doing so; similarly, if you return the product or products at our expense, we may pass that expense on to you. We will usually refund money using the same method used to make the payment. We will process the refund due to you as a result of a cancellation on the basis described in this section as soon as possible and, in any case, within the period of 30 days following the day we receive your valid notice of cancellation. Warranties and representations You warrant and represent to us that: you are legally capable of entering into binding contracts; you have full authority, power and capacity to agree to these terms and conditions; all the information that you provide to us in connection with your order is true, accurate, complete and non–misleading; and you will be able to take delivery of the products in accordance with these terms and conditions and our delivery policy. We warrant to you that: we have the right to sell the products that you buy; the products we sell to you are sold free from any charge or encumbrance, except as specified in these terms and conditions; you shall enjoy quiet possession of the products you buy, except as specified in these terms and conditions; the products you buy will correspond to any description published on our website; and the products you buy will be of satisfactory quality. These terms and conditions set out all of our warranties and representations relating to the supply of products hereunder. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law and subject to Section 11.1, all other warranties and representations are expressly excluded. Breach of product warranty If you believe that products you have purchased from us breach any of the warranties set out in Section 9.2, please contact us to discuss the issue and arrangements for the return of the products. If products you purchase from us do not conform with the warranties set out in Section 9.2, then you will be entitled to a refund of all amounts paid in respect of those products. Alternatively and subject to availability, we may agree to supply you with replacement products, in which case we will pay the cost of delivering those replacement products to you. In either case we will reimburse you for your reasonable expenses incurred in returning the products to us. If you return a product in contravention of these terms and conditions, and you do not have any other legal right to a refund or exchange in respect of that product: we will not refund the purchase price or exchange the product; we may retain the returned product until you pay to us such additional amount as we may charge for re–delivery of the returned product; and if we do not receive payment of such additional amount within 14 days of issuing a request for payment, we may destroy or otherwise dispose of the returned product in our sole discretion without any liability to you. Limitations and exclusions of liability Nothing in these terms and conditions will: limit or exclude any liability for death or personal injury resulting from negligence; limit or exclude any liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation; limit any liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or exclude any liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law, and, if you are a consumer, your statutory rights will not be excluded or limited by these terms and conditions, except to the extent permitted by law. The limitations and exclusions of liability set out in this Section 11 and elsewhere in these terms and conditions: are subject to Section 11.1; and govern all liabilities arising under these terms and conditions or relating to the subject matter of these terms and conditions, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort (including negligence) and for breach of statutory duty. We will not be liable to you in respect of any losses arising out of any event or events beyond our reasonable control. We will not be liable to you in respect of any business losses, including (without limitation) loss of or damage to profits, income, revenue, use, production, anticipated savings, business, contracts, commercial opportunities or goodwill. You accept that we have an interest in limiting the personal liability of our officers and employees and, having regard to that interest, you agree that you will not bring any claim personally against our officers or employees in respect of any losses you suffer in connection with the website or these terms and conditions (this will not, of course, limit or exclude the liability of the limited liability entity itself for the acts and omissions of our officers and employees). Our aggregate liability to you in respect of any contract to purchase products from us under these terms and conditions shall not exceed the total amount paid and payable to us under the contract. Order cancellation We may cancel any contract made under these terms and conditions immediately, by giving you written notice of termination, if: you fail to pay, on time and in full, any amount due to us under the contract; or you commit any breach of the terms of the contract. We may cancel a contract to supply a product or products made under these terms and conditions by written notice to you if we are prevented from fulfilling that contract by any event beyond our reasonable control, including without limitation any unavailability of raw materials, components or products, or any power failure, industrial dispute affecting any third party, governmental regulations, fire, flood, disaster, riot, terrorist attack or war. Consequences of order cancellation If a contract made under these terms and conditions is cancelled in accordance with Section 12: we will cease to have any obligation to deliver products which are undelivered at the date of cancellation; you will continue to have an obligation where applicable to pay for products which have been delivered at the date of cancellation (without prejudice to any right we may have to recover the products); and all the other provisions of these terms and conditions will cease to have effect, except that Sections 1.3, 6.4, 11, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20 and 21 will survive termination and continue in effect indefinitely. Scope These terms and conditions do not constitute or contain any assignment or licence of any intellectual property rights. These terms and conditions do not govern the licensing of works (including software and literary works) comprised or stored in products. These terms and conditions do not govern the provision of any services by us or any third party in relation to the products (other than delivery services). Variation We may revise these terms and conditions from time to time by publishing a new version on our website. A revision of these terms and conditions will govern contracts made under these terms and conditions at any time following the time of the revision, but will not affect contracts made before the time of the revision. Assignment You hereby agree that we may assign, transfer, sub–contract or otherwise deal with our rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions—providing, if you are a consumer, that such action does not serve to reduce the guarantees benefiting you under these terms and conditions. You may not without our prior written consent assign, transfer, sub–contract or otherwise deal with any of your rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions. No waivers No breach of any provision of these terms and conditions will be waived except with the express written consent of the party not in breach. No waiver of any breach of any provision of these terms and conditions shall be construed as a further or continuing waiver of any breach of that provision or any other provision of these terms and conditions. Severability If a provision of these terms and conditions is determined by any court or other competent authority to be unlawful and/or unenforceable, the other provisions will continue in effect. If any unlawful and/or unenforceable provision of these terms and conditions would be lawful or enforceable if part of it were deleted, that part will be deemed to be deleted, and the rest of the provision will continue in effect. Third party rights These terms and conditions are for our benefit and your benefit, and are not intended to benefit or be enforceable by any third party. The exercise of the parties’ rights under these terms and conditions is not subject to the consent of any third party. Entire agreement Subject to Section 11.1, these terms and conditions, together with our delivery policy and our returns policy, constitute the entire agreement between you and us in relation to the sale and purchase of our products and supersede all previous agreements between you and us in relation to the sale and purchase of our products. Law and jurisdiction These terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with Scottish law. Any disputes relating to these terms and conditions shall be subject to the jurisdiction of the courts of Scotland. Statutory and regulatory disclosures We will not file a copy of these terms and conditions specifically in relation to each user or customer and, if we update these terms and conditions, the version to which you originally agreed will no longer be available on our website. We recommend that you consider saving a copy of these terms and conditions for future reference. These terms and conditions are available in the English language only. Our details This website is owned and operated by dylan harris; dylan harris lives and works in the luxembourg; You can email corrupt press at dh@corruptpress.com. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>terms & conditions of sale</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>corrupt press poetry publisher luxembourg esch-sur-alzette english</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/info/submissions.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : corrupt press submissions Unfortunately, I cannot give the press the attention it needs at the moment, so cannot in all fairness accept any submissions. Please accept my apologies. Guidelines (not rules): Familiarise yourself with the (now withdrawn) advice from the Poetry Book Society. For chapbooks, submit between 8 and 18 pages of poems, for publication as A5. For collections, include at least 70 pages of poems for publication as US Trade (6x9 inches). The poems should excite, not in the ‘Bristol Rovers win the FA Cup’ way, but by their very nature—although Bristol Rovers excitement on top is welcome. Innovative work, especially innovate language, is particularly welcome. Traditional fayre (ho ho) is fine too, provided it’s done well—but absolutely no tiredness, clichés or overfamiliar phrases. Be particularly careful with rhyme; make it devious, not glaring from exhaustion. Some poems should have been previously published in magazines. It’s good when a book work as a whole, perhaps with something common between the poems (theme, subject, form, language; whatever, it’s up to you). Mixed language poems are welcome, but the dominant language should be English. Visual poetry, poetry with imagery, imaginary poetry: all are welcome, but colour might be difficult for a full collection. You should expect, and be able to handle, critical comments as part of the editorial process. This isn’t to condemn panache, but to point out oddities and possible errors: it’s those you’ve not noticed that make the process essential. Priority will be given to residents of non–anglophone countries. Please, no double submissions (submitting the same manuscript to two presses concurrently). If circumstances force it upon you, tell us. No plain old prose, sorry (prose poems are fine). Send your work to submissions@corruptpress.net, as follows: The poems should be in one file, in appropriate order, in PDF, rich text (RTF), or plain text (TXT) format. If layout is important to your work, use Pages, Publisher, or InDesign (CS5.5 format or earlier) and avoid word processors such as Word because they can change layout to suite the system used to view them. If fonts are significant, send a PDF with the fonts embedded. If you’re not sure, ask. For publication, any images should be prepared as high resolution TIFF files, at least 300 dots per inch. Do not create the TIFF by converting a lower resolution image. However, when submitting, send smaller JPeg or PNG files. You should include a list of your previous books, if any, including their title, publisher, publisher’s city, and year of publication. You should list the magazines which have published, or are going to publish, any of the poems in your submission. Include a short bio, a passport sized portrait of the poet, and your contact details. IMPORTANT: a portrait does not have to be a traditional image of a face. If you’re shy, get creative. Remember, though, the image will be small, so ensure it doesn’t depend on detail to work. Corrupt press has unfortunately been poor at replying promptly to submitting poets, for which the press apologises. Please do not presume there’s something wrong with your work if it is rejected. It could be that the work is fine but just doesn’t fit the direction the press is taking. If your work is accepted, and you agree to publication, it will be published under the following terms and conditions. If you find them unacceptable, it would be preferable not to submit a manuscript in the first place, as these terms are non–negotiable. We want world rights. We do not pay advances. Authors receive 10 free copies of their book. Authors may acquire further copies of their book at any time: if purchased before publication date, the discount is 50% of retail price; after publication, the discount is 40%. P&P will be charged if necessary. We do not accept payment from authors to publish their books. We include termination clauses so the author can exit their contract with 6 months’ notice, after 3 years have elapsed, without penalty. We offer royalties of 10% of the retail price, but this kicks in only after 150 copies have been sold. Thus, income on the first 150 copies is entirely for the press. Thereafter we share. We welcome approaches from beyond Luxembourg, where the press is currently based. Note, though, that there are limits to the amount of support that we can offer. We will not pay permissions fees, for reprints, for illustrations, or for quoted texts. We try to reply to all submissions quickly, but there are times when we fall behind. If you do not hear within two or three months, we do not mind being chased for a reply. Decisions are final, and we will not enter into further discussions concerning rejected manuscripts. We reserve the right to control the design of our books and their covers, although we will try to take the author’s wishes into account when doing so. We do not arrange reading tours or publicity, but can sometimes arrange readings in Paris, and occasionally manage to arrange some elsewhere. There are practical limits to this, though, given the nature of the Paris reading scene and the general lack of funds to support it. If the submitted poetry is placed online, visible to the public, that’s not a problem—but please inform us, & link to us. These terms are based on those of Shearsman Press, with permission. dylan harris corrupt press : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>submissions</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>corrupt press poetry publisher luxembourg esch-sur-alzette english</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/info/thanx.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : corrupt press thank you for your purchase Thank you for your purchase. It has been completed successfully, and a receipt has been emailed to you. You may log on to your paypal account to view details of this transaction. Click here to continue shopping. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>thank you</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>corrupt press poetry publisher luxembourg esch-sur-alzette english</keywords>
</page>
<page>
<url>/info/use.shtml</url>
<content>: : home : : about ○ authors ○ books ○ submissions ○ view cart : : corrupt press terms & conditions of use Introduction These terms and conditions govern your use of our website. By using our website, you accept these terms and conditions in full; accordingly, if you disagree with these terms and conditions or any part of these terms and conditions, you must not use our website. If you register with our website or make a purchase on our website, we will ask you to expressly agree to these terms and conditions. You must be at least 18 years of age to use our website; and by using our website or agreeing to these terms and conditions, you warrant and represent to us that you are at least 18 years of age. Copyright notice Copyright © 2011–2021 dylan harris. Subject to the express provisions of these terms and conditions: we, together with our licensors, own and control all the copyright and other intellectual property rights in our website and the material on our website; and all the copyright and other intellectual property rights in our website and the material on our website are reserved. Licence to use website You may: view pages from our website in a web browser; download pages from our website for caching in a web browser; print pages from our website; stream audio and video files from our website; and use our website services by means of a web browser, subject to the other provisions of these terms and conditions. Except as expressly permitted by Section 3.1 or the other provisions of these terms and conditions, you must not download any material from our website or save any such material to your computer. Except as expressly permitted by these terms and conditions, you must not edit or otherwise modify any material on our website. Unless you own or control the relevant rights in the material, you must not: republish material from our website (including republication on another website); sell, rent or sub–license material from our website; show any material from our website in public; exploit material from our website for a commercial purpose; or redistribute material from our website. Notwithstanding Section 3.4, you may redistribute our newsletter in print and electronic form to any person. We reserve the right to restrict access to areas of our website, or indeed our whole website, at our discretion; you must not circumvent or bypass, or attempt to circumvent or bypass, any access restriction measures on our website. Acceptable use You must not: use our website in any way or take any action that causes, or may cause, damage to the website or impairment of the performance, availability or accessibility of the website; use our website in any way that is unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful, or in connection with any unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful purpose or activity; use our website to copy, store, host, transmit, send, use, publish or distribute any material which consists of (or is linked to) any spyware, computer virus, Trojan horse, worm, keystroke logger, rootkit or other malicious computer software; conduct any systematic or automated data collection activities (including without limitation scraping, data mining, data extraction and data harvesting) on or in relation to our website without our express written consent; violate the directives set out in the robots.txt file for our website; or use data collected from our website for any direct marketing activity (including without limitation email marketing, SMS marketing, telemarketing and direct mailing). You must not use data collected from our website to contact individuals, companies or other persons or entities. You must ensure that all the information you supply to us through our website, or in relation to our website, is true, accurate, current, complete and non–misleading. Acceptable use You must not: use our website in any way or take any action that causes, or may cause, damage to the website or impairment of the performance, availability or accessibility of the website; use our website in any way that is unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful, or in connection with any unlawful, illegal, fraudulent or harmful purpose or activity; use our website to copy, store, host, transmit, send, use, publish or distribute any material which consists of (or is linked to) any spyware, computer virus, Trojan horse, worm, keystroke logger, rootkit or other malicious computer software; conduct any systematic or automated data collection activities (including without limitation scraping, data mining, data extraction and data harvesting) on or in relation to our website without our express written consent; violate the directives set out in the robots.txt file for our website; or use data collected from our website for any direct marketing activity (including without limitation email marketing, SMS marketing, telemarketing and direct mailing). You must not use data collected from our website to contact individuals, companies or other persons or entities. You must ensure that all the information you supply to us through our website, or in relation to our website, is true, accurate, current, complete and non–misleading. Products The advertising of products on our website constitutes an “invitation to treat” rather than a contractual offer. We may periodically change the products available on our website, and we do not undertake to continue to supply any particular product or type of product. Prices stated on our website may be stated incorrectly. The sale and purchase of products through our website will be subject to terms and conditions of sale, and we will ask you to agree to the terms of that document each time you make a purchase on our website. Limited warranties We do not warrant or represent: the completeness or accuracy of the information published on our website; that the material on the website is up to date; or that the website or any service on the website will remain available. We reserve the right to discontinue or alter any or all of our website services, and to stop publishing our website, at any time in our sole discretion without notice or explanation; and save to the extent that these terms and conditions expressly provide otherwise, you will not be entitled to any compensation or other payment upon the discontinuance or alteration of any website services, or if we stop publishing the website. To the maximum extent permitted by applicable law and subject to Section 8.1, we exclude all representations and warranties relating to the subject matter of these terms and conditions, our website and the use of our website. Limitations and exclusions of liability Nothing in these terms and conditions will: limit or exclude any liability for death or personal injury resulting from negligence; limit or exclude any liability for fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation; limit any liabilities in any way that is not permitted under applicable law; or exclude any liabilities that may not be excluded under applicable law. The limitations and exclusions of liability set out in this Section 8 and elsewhere in these terms and conditions: are subject to Section 8.1; and govern all liabilities arising under these terms and conditions or relating to the subject matter of these terms and conditions, including liabilities arising in contract, in tort (including negligence) and for breach of statutory duty. To the extent that our website and the information and services on our website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature. We will not be liable to you in respect of any losses arising out of any event or events beyond our reasonable control. We will not be liable to you in respect of any business losses, including (without limitation) loss of or damage to profits, income, revenue, use, production, anticipated savings, business, contracts, commercial opportunities or goodwill. We will not be liable to you in respect of any loss or corruption of any data, database or software. We will not be liable to you in respect of any special, indirect or consequential loss or damage. You accept that we have an interest in limiting the personal liability of our officers and employees and, having regard to that interest, you acknowledge that we are a limited liability entity; you agree that you will not bring any claim personally against our officers or employees in respect of any losses you suffer in connection with the website or these terms and conditions (this will not, of course, limit or exclude the liability of the limited liability entity itself for the acts and omissions of our officers and employees). Breaches of these terms and conditions Without prejudice to our other rights under these terms and conditions, if you breach these terms and conditions in any way, or if we reasonably suspect that you have breached these terms and conditions in any way, we may: send you one or more formal warnings; temporarily suspend your access to our website; permanently prohibit you from accessing our website; block computers using your IP address(es) from accessing our website; contact any or all your internet service providers and request that they block your access to our website; and/or commence legal action against you, whether for breach of contract or otherwise. Where we suspend or prohibit or block your access to our website or a part of our website, you must not take any action to circumvent such suspension or prohibition or blocking . Third party websites Our website includes hyperlinks to other websites owned and operated by third parties; such hyperlinks are not recommendations. We have no control over third party websites and their contents, and subject to Section 8.1 we accept no responsibility for them or for any loss or damage that may arise from your use of them. Variation We may revise these terms and conditions from time to time. The revised terms and conditions will apply to the use of our website from the date of their publication on the website, and you hereby waive any right you may otherwise have to be notified of, or to consent to, revisions of the terms and conditions. Assignment You hereby agree that we may assign, transfer, sub–contract or otherwise deal with our rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions. You may not without our prior written consent assign, transfer, sub–contract or otherwise deal with any of your rights and/or obligations under these terms and conditions. Severability If a provision of these terms and conditions is determined by any court or other competent authority to be unlawful and/or unenforceable, the other provisions will continue in effect. If any unlawful and/or unenforceable provision of these terms and conditions would be lawful or enforceable if part of it were deleted, that part will be deemed to be deleted, and the rest of the provision will continue in effect. Third party rights These terms and conditions are for our benefit and your benefit, and are not intended to benefit or be enforceable by any third party. The exercise of the parties’ rights under these terms and conditions is not subject to the consent of any third party. Entire agreement Subject to Section 8.1, these terms and conditions, together with our privacy and cookies policy, constitute the entire agreement between you and us in relation to your use of our website and supersede all previous agreements between you and us in relation to your use of our website. Law and jurisdiction These terms and conditions shall be governed by and construed in accordance with luxembourg law. Any disputes relating to these terms and conditions shall be subject to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of The Grand Duchy of Luxembourg. Our details This website is owned and operated by dylan harris; dylan harris lives and works in the luxembourg; You can email corrupt press at dh@corruptpress.com. : : contact ○ terms of use ○ privacy & cookies ○ terms of sale ○ returns ○ delivery : : : :dylan harris trades as corrupt press ○ © 2011–2021 dylan harris : :</content>
<title>terms & conditions of use</title>
<author>dylan harris</author>
<description>corrupt press is a small poetry press</description>
<keywords>corrupt press poetry publisher luxembourg esch-sur-alzette english</keywords>
</page>
